片名：鋼鐵擂臺/鐵甲鋼拳
翻譯：閑閑的猛男 校對：目前沒有
翻譯的很辛苦 句句推敲 認為好的按聲贊 但是轉載 請考慮原創的辛苦 不要把原訊息刪掉！
等一下 等一下 來了
Hang on, hang on. Come on.
Charlie你在哪里？更重要的是 幾時還錢？
Where are you, Charlie? More importantly, where is my money?
- 你還欠我三萬元 - Jack 我馬上可以還你
- You're into me for 30 grand. - Jack, I'm going to pay you.
我不是Jack 我是比爾
This ain't Jack! It's Bill Panner.
你還欠Jack錢？你最好先還我
You owe Jack money, too? You pay me first!
比爾 兄弟 錢我準備好了 就在我手上
Bill. We're good, buddy. I got your money. It's right here in my hand.
那我們約個地………
Why don't we meet up on the?
- 喂？你的訊號很差 - 我聽不到你
- Your phone's going all screwy. Hello? - I'm losing you.
我聽不清楚你說什么...
I can't hear what you're say...
先生您好 那個是突擊者號嗎？
Hey, mister. Is that Ambush?
- 是的 - 我們可以看看嗎？
- Yeah. - Can we see him?
- 你們想看？- 耶
- You want to see him? - Yeah.
等一下！
Give me a minute.
這個是...
This...
...突擊者號！ 啟動 啟動！
is Ambush. Wakey, wakey.
- 他要跟誰比賽？- 其實他是要跟...
- What robot is he fighting? - Actually he's going to fight...
噢 小妹妹 你要干嘛？
Whoa, little lady. What are you doing?
我可不可以跟他照個像？
Can we get a picture with him?
當然可以 五塊錢
Sure. For five dollars.
照個像要五元？你開玩笑吧？
You want five dollars? Seriously?
沒開玩笑 馬上給我五元
No, I want five dollars immediately.
走吧！小朋友！
Come on, guys.
- 好啦！我開玩笑的 三元就好 - 你慢慢想吧
- All right, I'm kidding. Three bucks. - Whatever.
- 那就二塊半好了？- 你這個遜?！
- How about $2.50? - You suck!
又是一個鄉巴佬小鎮 是吧？
It's going to be one of those towns, huh?
各位先生女士們 歡迎來到2020年圣蘭卓鄉村市集
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to the 2020 San Leandro County Fair.
各位請坐 我們將要開始了
Please take your seats. We're almost ready to get this thing started.
講好的是我的機器人對抗800磅的牛
I was told my bot was fighting an 800-pound steer.
那只牛絕對不止800磅 你這個呆頭
That is not 800 pounds, knucklehead.
Charlie"無所不能小子" 肯頓 看來你也老了 老朋友
Charlie "the Can Do Kid" Kenton. Time has not been good to you, my friend.
- 里奇 麻煩大了 - 不要激動 老朋友
- Ricky, we got a big problem here. - Slow down there, hoss.
最后一次我們的見面是在桑休士頓中心
Last time I saw you, you were staring at the ceiling at the Sam Houston Center
我正好賞你一記右叉拳
with the taste of my right cross all over your face.
- 準備好了嗎？- 耶
- Are we good to go here? - Yeah.
說好的是我的機器人對抗800磅的牛 代價是三千元
We agreed that my boxer would fight an 800-pound steer for three grand.
- 真的嘛？- 是的 說好的是這樣
- Am I right? - Yes, sir. We did.
但是那只牛看起來大概是2000磅
That bull is like 2,000 pounds.
打個商量
I'll tell you something.
如果你的機器人不打 你一分錢都拿不到 怎么樣？
Your bot don't fight, you don't get paid! How about that?
滾吧你！
Get the hell out of here.
要不要賭大一點 我的機器人跟你的牛對打
Why don't we make this more interesting. My bot against your bull, straight up.
- 賭多少？- 二萬 勝方獨贏
- How much? - Twenty grand, winner takes all.
- 二萬？你有錢可以賭？- 藏在我車上
- Twenty grand. You got 20 grand? - In a safe in my truck.
Charlie 好吧！
All right, Charlie.
二萬就二萬 但是如果你輸了繞跑
Twenty grand it is, but if you lose and you welch,
我見你一次就海扁你一次
I'll come after you and beat you to within an inch of your life.
你知道我沒騙你 因為我時常在扁你
You know that I can do that because I already done done it!
別靠我那么那么近 你這個拳擊場上的娘娘腔 到底比不比？
In life you get too close, in the ring you stand back like a girl. Just shake.
那好 握手然后“?” 像以前一樣 你要不要再被我扁？
All right. Shake and pow! Just like that once again. You want to dance again?
幫這家伙加加油 給他點好運 他需要點運氣 耶！
Cheer for this guy. Give him some luck. He needs some luck, y'all.
不要再惹那只牛！
Don't touch that bull.
各位先生女士們 我來問一下；
Ladies and gentlemen, I got to ask,
這里有沒有人是機器人拳擊賽的粉絲？
do we have any fans of robot boxing here today?
各位好朋友 注意聽著 我了解………
Now, listen, friends, I understand
不是每個人都可以付得起300元的門票
we can't all afford to go all the way over there to Dallas
然后一路到達拉斯去看世界杯機器人拳擊大賽！
and pay $300 for one of those World Robot Boxing League fights.
所以我決定給你們帶來一場機器人拳擊比賽
So, I decided that I would bring a robot boxing match
就在這里 我們的圣卓蘭鄉村市集上
right here to our little fair here in San Leandro.
喜歡嗎？
How about that?
各位先生女士們 我來介紹
Ladies and gentlemen, I introduce to you,
突擊者號！
Ambush!
來吧 開始吧！
Let's do it!
好樣的 大家伙
All right, big fella.
他是不是一個大家伙啊？
He's a big fella, ain't he?
轉一圈 讓大家看看你有多威猛！
Take a turn. Let them see how beautiful you are.
看看你有多有力！
Show them some power.
大家趕快看 他在為我們表演功夫喔
Look at that. He's getting all kung fu-y on us.
耶 大家伙！
Yeah, big fella.
突擊者號的對手是年度公牛大賽……
Ambush's opponent today, he's last year's runner-up
擊倒率最高的………
in the baddest of the bulls competition,
各位先生女士們
ladies and gentlemen,
黑色閃電！
Black Thunder!
- 開始吧 - 戰斗開始咯
- Let's get it on! - Let's get this thing started.
你就這么點能耐？
Is that all you got?
耶！兄弟 干勁拿出來！
Yeah, brother. Bring it on.
干掉他 干掉他！
Take him, take him.
突擊者一掌把這只憤怒的牛翻倒在地
Ambush lays the smackdown on that prime beef.
我還有很多絕招 大家伙 我們才剛暖身
I got more for you, big fella. We're just getting started.
準備 現在 跳
OK. Jump, now!
突擊者一摑掀翻黑色閃電
Ambush, decks Black Thunder,
但是當你惹毛一只公牛 你就最好小心他們的牛角
but when you mess with the bull, you're going to get the horns.
噢 你喜歡是吧！我看得出來 妳喜歡這個
You like that. I can tell. You like that.
轉身小心
Turn around!
里奇！里奇！夠了我們認輸！
Ricky! Ricky, stop this thing!
來吧！我們還要戰斗 跳 跳一下 ！
Come on. We're still in this thing. Just hop. Hop.
就是這樣 來吧！
That's it. Come on.
里奇 夠了！ 我們認輸！
Ricky, enough! Enough!
你的機器人被痛扁的聲音蓋過了你的聲音
I can't hear you over the sound of your robot being destroyed.
殺了他！殺了他！殺了他！
Kill! Kill! Kill!
快點 站起來！
Come on, get up.
站起來！快點！
Get up! Come on!
不要！
No!
不要！不要！不要！
Come on, no. No, no, no!
各位先生女士們 讓我們為我們的勇士喝彩吧！
Ladies and gentlemen, let's hear it for our warriors out here today
就在今天 就在我們的圣蘭卓鄉村市集
at the 2020 San Leandro County Fair.
感謝你們的參觀
Thank you for coming out,
我保證下次會更精彩的
and we'll see you next time, because there will be one.
把腳還給我
Give me that leg.
可以 要五塊錢
Sure. For five dollars.
活該 ！
Boo-yah!
各位先生女士們 很好 不可思議的好玩對吧？
All right! That was ridiculous fun, now wasn't it, ladies and gentlemen?
Charlie男孩 等下我來拿錢 你最好準備好！
I'm going to come by for my money, Charlie boy. You best have it.
- 大家一起喊 "嗨！" - 嗨！
- Everybody say "hey!" - Hey!
- 大家一起喊 "喝！" - 喝！
- Everybody say "ho!" - Ho!
拽不起來了吧？哈哈！小機器人！
How about that? How you doing there, little robot?
我的鑰匙 他媽的！
My keys, damn it.
再靠近一步 我就狠狠的扁你一頓
One more step and I'll drop you like your girlfriend.
Charlie 不要緊張
Charlie, relax.
我不會付錢 那是不公平的比賽 甚至花了我最后一個機器人！
I'm not paying you. That was a bogus fight. It cost me my last robot.
- 讓我們先說 - 你還記得卡洛琳法羅嗎？
- Just listen to us. - Do you recall Caroline Fallon?
她是我的前女友 我已經十年沒見過她了 她想干嘛？
She's my ex-girlfriend. I haven't seen her in ten years. What does she want?
她死了
Nothing. She died.
你還記不記得Max
Do you recall Max Kenton?
他是我兒子 他應該已經九歲了
He's my son. He's got to be nine.
- 十一歲 - 十一歲 好吧！
- Eleven. - Eleven. OK.
他也死了？
Is he dead, too?
不 他還好好的 所以我們才來
No, he's fine. That's why we're here.
翻譯：閑閑的猛男 校對：目前沒有
今天法庭要判決Max 十一歲
This court is convened to address the custodial status
他的監護權的所屬
of one Max Kenton, age 11.
母親是剛過世的卡洛琳法羅 父親是Charlie肯頓
Mother, Caroline Fallon, deceased. Father, Charles Kenton.
黛博拉 法羅 巴恩 你是小男孩的阿姨嗎？
Debra Fallon Barnes, you're the boy's aunt.
是的 就像我所表達的 我的先生 馬文 他很健康
Yes. As I've already told you, my husband, Marvin, is wealthy,
我們可以好好的照顧Max
and we can more than provide for Max.
我認為這樣很好 但是根據德州的法律
I appreciate that, but per Texas state law, without a written will
如果他沒出席的生父Charlie肯頓
next of kin retains custody.
沒有放棄他的撫養權的話
Charles Kenton, who is aware of this custody hearing,
我們還在等他出席
and we are expecting him...
我要一個新的機器人
I need a new robot now.
我幫突擊者在下周六安排一場大比賽
I had a big fight for Ambush next Saturday.
我現在要趕去處理一件事
I got to show up with something.
大聲公要賣嗎？大聲公是殺手級的！
Noisy Boy is for sale? In his day, Noisy Boy was a killer.
多少錢？很劃算 有沒有其他的毛病？
How much? That's a good deal. What's wrong with him?
我要買
I can live with that.
但是我現在沒有錢
I don't have it.
Charlie肯頓在Max一出生的時候就沒有盡到父親的義務
Charles Kenton waived all of his rights to custody right after the boy was born.
我們可以更好地照顧Max
I can more than provide for Max.
你是Charlie肯頓嗎？
Please be Charles Kenton.
是的 就是Charlie
Charlie, yeah.
我來簽一些文件 放棄一些權力
I'm here to sign some paper that releases my rights
放棄我小孩的監護權
to the custody of my son.
所以我才來 我是應該來吧？
That's why I'm here. Do I need to be here?
Charlie
Charlie.
你還記得我嗎？
Do you even remember me?
- 黛博拉 卡洛琳的妹妹 - 是哦 黛博拉 你還好嗎？
- Debra, Caroline's sister. - Yeah, Debra. How are you?
肯頓先生 請坐！
Mr. Kenton. Please take a seat.
法官大人 我可以先去看看我的外甥嗎？
Your Honor, may I please go and see my nephew now?
可以！請去吧！
Yes, you may.
- 你呢？肯頓先生！ - 什么？
- How about you, Mr. Kenton? - What?
如果你想要 你可以跟你兒子獨處一會兒！
You can spend some time with him, if you'd like.
- 跟我兒子？- 是的 你兒子！
- With the kid? - Yeah, the kid.
- Max 你兒子！ - 好的！
- Max. Your son? - All right.
你跟機器人在一起太久了 現在也像機器一樣沒有感情
You've been working with those robots for so long, you've become one.
寶貝 你在這里等一下 我馬上回來
Honey, you wait right here. I'm going to be back.
甜心 不急 慢慢來！
You take all the time you need, sweetheart.
法官大人 如果可以的話 這么重要的事
Your Honor, I'd like to, at this juncture,
我想出去一下跟我的律師商量一下！
step out and call my attorney, if that's all right.
當然可以！
Please.
來吧！你怎么還不來？
Come on. Come on. There you are.
他會被領養的
He'll be in a foster home.
他們會找到一個年輕有活力的家庭的 是的！
No, they find good families. Young. Energetic. Yeah.
感謝你 麥克 我會的 好的
Thanks, Michael. I will. OK.
- 馬文巴恩 我是黛博拉的先生 - 是哦 耶！
- Marvin Barnes. I'm Debra's husband. - Right, yeah.
黛博拉是真的很想領養Max
Debra really wants to adopt Max.
- 我是很想完成他的愿望 - 七萬五千元
- I'm up for it. But... - Seventy-five grand.
七萬五千元？你是說真的？
$75,000? You're serious?
還有一件事是...
The thing is...
...我們這個夏天要去意大利度假
we're supposed to go to Italy this summer
跟我最好的朋友及他太太
with my oldest friend and his wife.
二個月都在圖斯卡尼
Two months in Tuscany and all over.
只有你們四個 聽起來不錯！
Just the four of you. Sounds nice.
我們八月底才會回來紐約
We'll be back in New York by the end of August.
到八月 那就十萬
In August. A hundred.
- 十萬？- 沒錯
- $100,000? - You heard me.
- 你瘋了嗎？- 沒有比你太太還瘋
- You're crazy. - Not nearly as crazy as your wife
如果我把兒子的撫養權簽給了德州政府
if you tell her I just signed over that kid to the state of Texas.
那么你太太就得不到他想要的
There's a real way everyone gets what they want here.
所以我建議你這樣做
So here's what you're going to do.
你告訴你的太太我只會把撫養權給他
You're going to tell your wife I'll only sign over custody to her
如果我能跟我兒子共度一個暑假
if I get to spend the summer with the kid first.
就說我真的很愧疚
Just tell her how guilty she made me feel
我一直沒有盡到父親的責任
for being such a terrible absentee dad,
我多想補償小孩一些父親的天倫之樂
how I want to make good with junior, a little fatherly bonding, whatnot.
她會買賬的 然后大家都得到自己想要的
She'll buy it, you get to be the hero and everybody wins.
好吧 但是不準告訴黛伯拉有關錢的事
OK. But not a word about the money to Debra, you understand?
我了解
I understand.
今晚我們載Max過去的時候 我會先付你五萬塊
I'll give you 50 grand tonight when we drop off Max
然后等我們八月回來 再付你五萬
and the other 50 when we get back in August
而且你要帶他到紐約給我們
and you deliver him to us in New York.
很高興跟你做生意
Pleasure doing business with you.
法官大人 很高興我們都仔細的考慮
Your Honor, I'm happy we all took the time
作出對每個人都好的決定
to make the best decision for everyone.
- 高興嗎？- 是的 是我
- Happy? - Yeah, it's me.
我要買下大聲公 我有錢了
I'm buying Noisy Boy. I got the money.
把它帶到泰利健身房 我等一下就到
Take him to Tallet's Gym and I'll meet you there.
哈?？
Hello?
百麗？
Bailey?
有人在這里等你付錢
Some guy is here with the robot you're buying,
千萬不要放我鴿子
and it smells like disaster to me.
我也很高興見到你
Nice to see you, too.
- 你知道你很可愛嗎？- 少來一套
- Might I also say how cute you look. - Give it up.
天啊 我要沖個涼 你也要嗎？一起來吧！
God, I need a shower. You want to take a shower? Come on.
我要說清楚一件事
Let me make something clear.
有個可怕的人帶著個機器人
A creepy dude with a robot in a box
坐在健身房門口等我二個小時了
has been sitting outside my gym for two hours.
如果暫時先不考慮這件在我家門口的黑市交易
Putting aside the fact that you're doing
你怎么付這個錢？
what I'm guessing is a black market deal on my doorstep,
你不是剛毀了突擊者號？
how will you pay him when Ambush just got destroyed?
錢快到了 安撫他一下！
The money is on its way. Just distract him.
我一直在安撫他 我快累死了！
I have been. It's exhausting.
- 你最好了 - 耶？是嗎？
- You're the best. - Yeah? Really?
那就是你剛買了四萬五千元的機器人但是你還欠我六千的房租？
Is that why you're buying a $45,000 robot when you owe me six grand in rent?
- 因為我最好說話？- 三千
- Because I'm the best? - Three.
六千 而且告訴你 已經有人要買下我的地方了
Six. There is a guy with real money who wants to buy this place.
少來了 你不會真的想賣掉你老爸留給你的健身房？
Come on. Like you're really going to sell your dad's gym.
如果你不付房租 我也付不出錢 那我就逼不得已了
If you don't make rent, I can't make payments and I won't have a choice.
你父親會從墳墓里面爬起來踢你的
Your father would climb out of his grave and kick your ass
- 如果你賣了這個地方 - 我父親會爬出他的墳墓
- if you sold this place. - My father would climb out of his grave
踢你的屁股
and kick your ass.
百麗？
Bailey?
- 不要 - 不要做什么？
- Don't. - Don't what?
不要那么做
Don't do that.
- 不要做什么？- 不要做那種小狗表情
- Don't what? - Don't do that thing.
- 不對 你喜歡拳擊 - 不對
- No, you like that thing. - No.
- 是的 - 不對 我不喜歡拳擊
- Yeah. - No, I don't like that thing.
我習慣了 簡單地說 但是我現在喜歡錢
I used to. Once. Briefly. Now I like money more.
- 我不相信你 - 我不管
- I don't believe you. - I don't care.
馬文
Marvin.
錢到了
Your money has arrived.
馬文
Marv.
五萬 說好的
Fifty grand, as promised.
這個是我們的號碼及我們在歐洲的聯絡方式
Here are all our numbers and contact info over in Europe.
嗯 所以都安排好了
So that's everything there.
馬文告訴我你想跟馬克思小聚一段時間
So Marvin tells me you want this time with Max.
- 是的 - 你做的很對
- Yeah. - You did the right thing,
把監護權給我
giving me custody.
卡洛琳也會希望你這么做
Caroline would have wanted that.
現在 請八月27號準時帶Max到紐約給我們
Now, have him back in New York on August 27th.
沒問題
That's a deal.
好的 我們去接Max 好的 ？我們去接Max
OK, let's go get Max. OK? Let's get Max.
還好嗎？你要到另外一邊 我來帶Max？
It's OK. You want to go around the other side here and I'll get Max?
嗨 Max 再見 小老弟
Hey. Max. See you, pal.
親愛的Max 我們暑假過后見
Max, we'll see you at the end of the summer, honey.
我是Charlie
I'm Charlie.
好久不見了 我是...
It's been a long time. You know, I'm your...
- 你搞死我了 - 嘴巴真干凈
- You screwed me. - Nice mouth.
你知道他們現在要去哪里？
Do you know where they're going?
- 意大利？- 是啊 意大利
- Italy? - Yeah, Italy.
那我為什么要跟你呆在這個鳥地方？
So how did I get stuck here with you?
不要激動 你還有后面一輩子的時間跟他們在一起
Relax, kid. You got a whole life of fine living ahead of you.
Charlie
Charlie!
那個老兄氣瘋了 他要走了！
Dude's pissed. He's going to take off.
- 馬文給你錢了嗎？- 來 剛剛給了
- Did Marvin give you that money? - Here, just close the deal.
我等下過去 好嗎？
I'll be right there, OK?
- 我是百麗 - Max
- I'm Bailey. - Max.
Max 肯頓
Max Kenton.
- 這是你的... - 是的我兒子
- So this is your... - Yeah, it's him.
不要擔心好嗎？
Don't worry about it, OK?
我要照顧你們二個跟...
I'm looking at you two and...
請把大聲公放在店里好嗎？謝謝你！
Just go and put Noisy in the shop, please? Thank you.
我出去的時候 你跟百麗呆在店里好嗎？
You're going to stay here with her while I'm on the road.
- 他給你多少錢？- 你誤會了
- How much did he give you? - You're coming at this the wrong way.
不 告訴我 我要知道
No, tell me. I want to know.
好吧！五萬元
Fifty thousand, OK?
他給我五萬元來讓我放棄你
He gave me $50,000 to sign you over to her.
你可以住嘴嗎？
Will you shut up now?
你把我賣了？
You sold me?
沒有那么糟！
Sounds worse than it is.
- 真的？- 那是對你最好的
- Really. - It's to take care of you.
那我要分賬分一半
Give me half the money and you won't have to.
- 你要去哪里？- 把錢給我 我自己會照顧自己
- Where are you going to go? - Give me the money. I'll be fine.
我答應你阿姨 暑假結束的時候會送你去紐約的
I told your aunt I'll get you to New York at the end of the summer.
現在你只在乎黛博拉阿姨？
Now you're concerned for Aunt Debra?
你用五萬把我賣掉 你欠我二萬五
You sold me for 50 grand. You owe me half!
我沒有錢 我把錢花在機器人身上 花完了 沒錢了！
I don't have it! I spent the money on a robot. It's gone! OK? Gone!
我完蛋了
I'm through here.
你買了什么？
What do we got?
大聲公到了
Noisy Boy has arrived.
貼滿了海關及航空公司的標簽
That's a lot of airline stickers and customs tags.
- 他到過世界的每個角落 - 倫敦 日本 巴西 巴爾的摩...
- He's been all over the world. - London, Japan, Brazil, S鉶 Paulo...
這二年還沒有到過北美
Hasn't seen North American soil in over two years.
或許是因為這樣 價格才那么便宜 天才！
Maybe that's why you got such a good price, genius.
決定留下來了？
Decided to stay?
百麗會照顧你幾個禮拜
This is Bailey. She'll be looking after you for a few weeks.
這幾周請幫我照顧小孩
I need you to look after the kid for a few weeks.
- 我要一半的錢 - 你還要討論這個？
- I want half that money. - Are we back to this again?
那個是真正的搏擊機器人？
Is there a real robot boxer in there?
大聲公 你有沒有聽過它？
Noisy Boy's in there. You ever heard of him?
當然 它在2016年跟羅比肯爭奪世界冠軍
Of course. He fought Rubicon for the WRB belt in 2016.
老天爺 他看起來太好了！
Holy crap, he looks amazing.
它的盔甲已經換過了 我們看看里面的零件是不是一樣好
His composite armor has been replaced. Let's see if the insides look as good.
我已經反復看過他跟羅比肯的比賽快20次了
I've watched that fight with Rubicon like 20 times.
它實在應該在第三回合擊敗他的
He should have had him in the third round,
但是羅比肯打出一記幸運的右拳 結束了！
but Rubicon got lucky with a huge right and ended it.
不要激動 他現在是我們的了
Relax, kid, he's on our side.
- 不好玩 - 有點好玩
- Not funny. - Kind of funny.
你知道他有聲控裝置吧？
You know he has voice recognition, right?
- 不 沒有吧？- 他不是普通級別的
- No, he doesn't. - He didn't in the League.
當大聲公在巴西的時候 他們應該裝上的
When Noisy fought in Brazil, they must have put it in.
巴西人就是喜歡對機器人說話的那種怪?
Brazilians are crazy about that talk-to-your-robot crap.
右 左 上擊拳！
Right, left, uppercut!
壞掉了！ 右 左 上擊拳！
Doesn't work. Right, left, uppercut!
我就知道便宜沒好貨的
I knew that price was too good to be true. We got screwed.
- 讓我看看 我來修修看 - 看看它有多好吧！
- Let me see if I can fix it. - Look how good he looks, too.
二秒就好 我看看！
Give me two seconds. Let me look at something!
- 你為什么不驗驗貨？- 不要緊張
- Why didn't you ask to look at it? - Relax!
你是不是用日文？
Was that Japanese?
我看看可不可以切換到英文！
Let me see if I can reset him to English.
你怎么會講日文？
How do you know Japanese?
電視游戲
Video games.
你會玩日文游戲？
You play video games in Japanese?
走私來的日本游戲都比較好的
Japanese bootlegs are always better.
給我吧
Give me that.
已經改到英文模式 而且我找到他的命令集了
He's reset to English, and I found his command matrix.
制造商已經預設了很多的組合拳了
They have pre-loaded a bunch of combinations.
他們應該要附個說明書的
They should be listed here.
上下擊拳組合
Top salvo!
我早告訴你了
What did I tell you?
重拳下擊組合
Gravity One Downtown!
我真是太幸運了
I was due for some good luck!
- 不客氣 - 謝謝你
- You're welcome. - Thank you.
百麗 幫我裝上車 我要去賺妳的錢了
Bailey, help me put him in the truck. I am going to go and get your money.
- 把鑰匙給我 - 我要跟你一起去
- Give me the keys. - I'm coming with you.
- 你不能去 - 為什么？
- No, you're not. - Why not?
因為我不想讓你去 好嗎？
Because I don't want you with me, OK?
讓我一起去 不然你就只能到下水溝釣你的鑰匙了
I'm either coming with you, or you're fishing for your keys in the sewer.
老人家 你決定咯！
Your choice. What's it going to be, old man?
噢 老天爺 好險 快掉下去了噢
Oh, my God. That was close, wasn't it?
- 不要再那樣做 - 嚇到你了是吧？
- Don't do that again. - That's scaring you, isn't it?
不要再那樣做是嗎？
Don't do this again?
上車 馬上上車！把鑰匙給我先！
Get in. Just get in. Give me the keys first.
等我先上車再給你 大老爹！
Wait till I get in the truck. Thanks, Big Pops.
快樂的行程
Sweet ride.
系上安全帶 閉嘴！
Put on your seatbelt and don't talk.
我要談一下賭金
I'm taking all bets!
跟上 不要落后
Keep up. Stay close.
Charlie肯頓來了
Charlie Kenton is in the house!
- 很好 很好 - 進來 老兄！
- All right, all right. - Come on, man!
- 這個是大聲公嗎？- 是的 唯一的
- Is that Noisy Boy? - The one and only.
大聲公來了！
That's Noisy Boy!
大聲公是日本過來的 他們那里的拳擊有點軟
Noisy's been in Japan. Softer bots over there.
- 你確定今晚要打？- 你有哪些人？
- Sure you want to fight him tonight? - What do you got?
你知道的 他可以打敗這里的每一個機器人
He can take any bot in this place. You know it.
你可以隨意挑選你的對手
You can have any undercard you want.
五千的保證金
Five thousand guaranteed.
每一回合一千 如果你的機器人撐得過去
A thousand every round your bot survives.
直到倒下
Fight till the death!
不 給我最重要的壓軸
No. Give me the main event.
- 少來 - 這是大聲公哩
- Come on. - This is Noisy Boy.
這是松本原廠的機器人
An original Tak Mashido bot.
大聲公是世界級別的 拜托
He was a World Robot League boxer. Come on!
你要跟邁達斯打？
You want to fight Midas?
五萬保證金 贏家通吃！
Fifty thousand guaranteed, winner takes all.
- 五萬？真的 五萬？- 不開玩笑！
Fifty? Really, 50? Now you're talking.
等一下 聽我的 不 考慮一下！
Listen, listen. No, look.
- 聽我說一下！ - 等我一下
- Listen! - Give me a sec.
我們最好挑一些卡片上的對手 賺點現金離開這里
We should take an undercard fight, make a little cash and get out of here!
首先 不是“我們”
First, there is no "we."
第二 他會碾碎邁達斯 我可以賺一大筆
Second, he's going to crush Midas, and I'm going to make real cash!
我們會打敗邁達斯的！
We'll take Midas!
今晚 我們的壓軸！
Tonight, our main event
特別的金色血液的殺手
features the gold-blooded killer!
像龐克的痞子
This pimped-out punk
痛苦的制造者
is programmed for pain!
讓我們歡迎神奇的邁達斯
I give to you the mighty Midas!
對抗者是...
Against a bot
曾經出現在世界大賽決賽的大男孩
who ran with the big boys in the WRB!
他剛結束全世界之旅 剛回到家的
He's been on an exile tour overseas, but now he's back home,
而且已經準備好要制造很多的噪音
and he's ready to make some noise!
好久不見的...
Take your first look in a long time
大聲公
at Noisy Boy!
撞擊宮殿！
Crash Palace,
誰已經準備好要開始大撞擊了？
who's ready for some destruction?!
讓我們開始賺大錢了 來吧！
Let's make some money! Come on!
現在 邁達斯對抗大聲公
We have Midas against Noisy Boy.
大聲公對抗馬達斯
Noisy Boy against Midas.
你們等這個壓軸等了一整晚 就在撞擊宮殿！
You've been waiting all night for this match up, Crash Palace!
右拳半月彎刀！
Scimitar right!
你有看到嗎？
Did you see that?
太簡單了 錢真好賺 整晚都是這樣！
Easy money, easy money all night. All night long!
趕快起來！ 還沒有結束！來吧！
Come on! It's not over yet. Let's go!
面拳齊射！ ！交火！
Skull salvo! Firefight!
- 是的！ 上吧 制造噪音吧！！ - 你說卡片 是嗎？
- Yeah! Go, Noisy! - Undercard, huh?
激波拳
Shockfist!
來吧！幕府三連擊！
Get in there. Shogun Trinity!
干掉他！重力拳 直搗面門
Let's finish him. Gravity Slam, Uptown!
真TMD瘋了！
This son-of-a-bitch is crazy!
金屬的世仇 來吧！
Full Metal Feud! Bring it!
左拳！ 痛苦的革命者！
Southpaw! Pain Revolution!
讓我給你一個禮物
I got something for you.
你敢逃開？你沒有辦法躲開！
Don't you run from me! You can't run from me!
站起來
Get up!
犯規了
That's illegal!
這是地下拳擊 沒有規則的
This is the underworld. There are no rules!
現在我們看邁達斯發飆了
Now we're seeing the Midas touch.
不 手舉起來！
No. Hands up!
回到角落來 婊子 像男人一樣大口喘氣
Get back in that corner, bitch, and take this whooping like a man!
他要被干掉了...
He's getting killed in there!
用耳機組 告訴它怎么做！
It's a headset! You talk into it and you tell him what to do!
恐懼盾牌！
Panic Shield!
對了 對了 一二組合拳！
That's it. One-Two Overlord!
不 不 粉碎拳
No, no. Shatter Punch!
- 五連擊 - 嘗嘗這個
- Five Recall! - Get some!
賈布 賈布！
Jab, jab!
右環拳！
Right roundhouse!
大聲公是不是剛剛把它的機油濺到馬達斯臉上？
Did he just spit his juice in Midas's face?
千萬不可把機油濺到馬達斯臉上
No, you did not spit in Midas's face!
讓我們狂歡吧 撞擊宮殿！
It's party time now, Crash Palace!
用你的左拳！
Use your left!
大聲公試著用一只手來對抗
Noisy's trying to do something with his one arm!
但是邁達斯夾住了他！然后好好的教訓他！
But Midas pins him, and Daddy goes to work!
不 不 起來！
No, no! Get up!
吃這個！
Get some!
移動！ 離開角落！
Move! Get out of the corner!
邁達斯！邁達斯！邁達斯！
Midas! Midas! Midas!
有人已經準備好送上卡布奇諾了！
Somebody's ready to serve up a decappuccino!
我要送你一個大禮 準備好了？
I got something for you! You ready?
晚安！邁達斯的最后一擊！
Good night! That's a home run for Midas.
再見吧 大聲公！
And so long to Noisy Boy.
太遜了 你餓了嗎？
That sucked. You hungry?
我救回了大聲公的聲控控制面板
I saved what's left of Noisy's voice recognition board.
除了那個以外 已經變垃圾了 我要再找一個新機器人
Other than that, he's trash. I got to get a new robot together.
我需要一個主機 什么？
I need to find a mainframe. What?
- 我不喜歡漢堡 - 什么樣的小孩不喜歡漢堡？
- I hate hamburgers. - What kid hates burgers?
好吧 我可以多吃一些 這個給你喝
Fine. More for me. Here, drink this.
你根本不該參加那場打斗的
You never should have taken that fight.
真的？真的？多謝你 天才！
Really? Really? Thanks, genius.
你總是那么的沖動嗎？
Do you even think about the stuff you do before you do it?
你根本不知道怎么戰斗
You had no idea how to fight that fight.
你知道的組合拳碼根本不到一半
Those combination codes, you didn't know what half of them even meant.
你的狂妄自大害的它的屁股被踢成二半
You threw them in there cocky and half-assed.
- 你根本沒有給他機會 - 大聲公沒有那么棒！
- You never gave him a chance. - He wasn't that good.
大聲公是最好的機器人
Noisy Boy was a great robot.
曾經是 曾經是 大聲公以前是很好 以前是
Was. Was a great robot back in the League, back in the day.
但是看看周圍 這里是偉大的機器人毀掉的墳場
But look around you. This place is where once great robots go to die.
那就丟掉它？
So throw him away.
這就是你 是吧？你不需要的 就丟掉？
That's what you do, right? Anything you don't need you throw away.
哇
Wow.
這會是漫長的一夜
It's been a long night.
如果你要在里面睡 閉嘴 上車！
If you want to sleep indoors tonight, shut up and get in the truck.
不要這樣看著我 上車！
Don't look at me like that way. Get in the truck!
他們花400買大聲公的頭
They gave me 400 for his head.
你坐好 我要去找一些零件！
You stay put. I'm going to look for parts.
我也要去 那個飲料讓我很興奮
I'm coming with you. That drink has my heart pounding.
如果我自己坐在車里 我的頭會炸掉
If I sit in this truck by myself, my head will explode.
隨便你 但是要跟好
Whatever. Just keep up.
真背
Crap.
退后
Stay back.
好了 跟上！
All right, keep up.
這個探照燈是定時的 你只要知道時間間隔就好
These searchlights are automated, but you got to time them right,
所以跟緊
so stay close.
那就對了！
It's all right.
來吧 快點！
Come on, come on.
- 我們會被抓啦！ - 來啦！
- We're going to get caught. - Come on.
慢一點 小心一點
Easy, easy. Easy, easy.
快一點 下來這里 快快快
Quick, quick. Down in here! Go, go, go!
機器人都在東邊 我們要快一點通過這里
Robots are on the east side. We got to be quick in here.
過了這里就沒有探照燈了 快 跑！
Once we're through here, there's no more searchlights. Quick! Go!
- 到了 - 我們要找什么？
- Here it is. - What are we looking for?
可以組合機器人的任何東西
Anything I could use to put a fighting bot together.
- 嗨 你看 - 什么？
- Hey, look. - What?
太小了
It's so small.
耶 那個比你還要老
Yeah. That's before your time.
那個是第一代的戰斗機器人
That's a Generation One, the very first fighting bot.
他們被造的很像人類 越像越好
They wanted them to look like us. The more human, the better.
沒想到變得那么快 把這個放進拖車
Crazy how quick everything changed. Put that in the cart.
- 什么改變了？- 好問題 人類的拳擊
- What changed? - A good question. Human boxing.
- 已經退流行了 - 為什么？
- It just faded. - Why?
因為金錢改變了一切 人們要更血腥 更好看
Because the money moved on. People wanted more carnage, more show.
可以綜合巴西柔術 格雷西 日式忍者術
You had the whole Brazilian underground, the Gracies, the Machados,
泰拳...幾千種不同的武術糅合在一起
jiu-jitsu, Muay Thai, and a thousand styles in between.
全部在水泥地上的重擊
Full-on ground-and-pound.
- 看看這個 - 這是什么？
- Look at this. - What's that?
我也不知道
I don't know.
不錯的零件
Not bad. Good spot.
如果還是一個拳手 人類的身體
You still had human fighters, human bodies,
你沒有辦法給人們他們想要的
so you couldn't give the people what they really wanted:
真相是 沒有圍欄的暴力 這就是人們想要的
True, no-holds-barred violence.
所以符合邏輯的下一步
The next logical step,
把人們移開 讓機器來自相殘殺
get the humans out of there and let the machines kill each other.
你會想念真正的拳擊嗎？
Do you miss it?
- 拳擊 你想念嗎？- 小心
- Boxing. Do you miss it? - Careful.
什么？我想知道
What? I want to know.
小心一點 你下面是個峭壁
Careful, you're on a cliff.
那下面很深 如果你掉下去 你就絕對...
That's a long way down. If you fell, you'd definitely...
Charlie 救我！
Charlie, help me!
Charlie！
Charlie!
- Charlie！ - Max！
- Charlie! - Max! Max!
Max！
Max!
- 不要動！ - 有一個機器人的手勾住了我
- Try not to move! - I'm on some sort of robot arm.
等一下！ 不要動 千萬不要動 把手伸過來 慢一點 輕一點
Wait! Just easy, easy. Give me your hand. Nice and easy.
要很慢很慢 很好 不要看下面 看著我 看著我 ！
Very slowly. Good. Don't look down. Look at me. Look at me.
就是這樣！ 我抓住你了！不用怕了 我抓住你了
That's it! I've got you! You don't have to be scared. I got you!
- 下面好深啊 - 沒問題了 我抓住你了！
- It's so far! - It's OK. I got you.
把手給我 慢一點 輕一點
Give me your other hand. Nice and slow.
只要動你的手 把你的手伸過來 慢慢的 遞過來
Just give me your other hand very slowly. Reach back. Come on. Reach!
看著我 我們一起來
Look at me. We're going to do this together.
就是你跟我 看著我 對的！
You and me. Just look at me. That's it.
一 二 三！
One... two... three!
就是這樣 我抓住你了 我抓住你了！
That's it. I got you! I got you. I got you. I got you.
你安全了 你安全了！
You're safe. You're safe.
沒事了 我抓住你了
All right, I got you.
- 你還好嗎？- 還好
- You all right? - Yeah.
過來這里 慢一點 慢一點
Come here. Easy. Easy.
你還好嗎？
You all right?
- 你還好嗎？- 是的
- You all right? - Yeah.
我告訴你很危險了
I told you it was dangerous.
小心一點 我們還在懸崖邊上
Careful. We're still on the edge here.
Charlie 我看到一整個機器人了
Charlie, I think there's a whole robot in there.
那又怎么樣？走吧！來吧
So what? Let's go. Come on.
我要帶走它 他救了我一命！
I'm taking him with me. He saved my life.
他沒有救你一命 是我救得 走吧！
He did not save your life. I saved your life. Let's go.
把推車推到邊上 我會用卷線拉上去！
Just bring the cart to the edge. I'll use the winch to get him out.
你要撿這個垃圾 你自己推車 我不玩了
You want that piece of junk? You get the cart yourself. I'm through here.
這是大聲公剩下的零件？
This is what's left of Noisy Boy?
是的
That's it.
他的頭已經變成撞擊宮殿大門上的裝潢了
His head does make a nice addition to the front of the Crash Palace.
- 正經一點 - 我們再做一個機器人
- It's not funny. - Let's get a robot, you and me.
好點子 只不過你破產了 我也快了
Good idea. You're broke. I'm almost there myself.
- 你搞砸了你最好的一次機會了 - 我們可以一起做出來的
- You destroyed the best shot you had. - We'll put one together.
你是那么聰明 這里又有那么多好零件
You're brilliant at this. There's good stuff here.
- 這里什么都沒有 - 有啊 你看！
- There's nothing here. - There is. Look.
這些都是垃圾... 垃圾
All your junk is... it's junk.
你甚至已經沒有辦法參加比賽了
You're not even in the game any more.
- 都是垃圾 - 我知道了 都是垃圾
- It's all garbage. - I heard you. It's garbage.
不要對我大聲
Don't get loud with me.
- 這是你自己的麻煩 - 你這是什么意思？
- You're your problem. - What's that supposed to mean?
我已經在這里幫你很長一段時間了
I have been here for you a long time.
臺上 臺下 還有這個物價上升 已經煩夠了
In the ring, out of the ring, and the whole ugly spiral down, and I'm tired.
我父親投資所有的財產支持你的拳擊 我們愛...
My father invested everything he had in your fight career. We loved...
他把你當成自己親人來照顧 這里是他的家
He loved you like family. And this is his home.
我努力的維持住這個家 讓他不要破碎！
I'm just trying not to let it die. That's my plan.
你呢？
What's yours?
你放棄了 是吧？
You're done, right?
你終于放棄了？因為我真的TMD確定 Charlie
You're finally done? Because I sure as hell am, Charlie.
我什么都沒有了
I got nothing left.
好吧
All right.
或許這里面還有點東西
Maybe there's something here.
昨天晚上小鬼帶回來的機器人 你可以幫我看看嗎？
This robot the kid brought in last night. Would you look at it for me?
拜托！
Please?
我從沒有看過這一型的機器人 它應該是第二代的
I've never seen anything like it before. He's Generation Two, but barely.
我找到一個適合他的電池 然后我用舊型的G-2 無線連上他
I found a power cell that fits him, and I hooked him up to this old G-2 remote.
你可以讓他動起來 但是他還是垃圾
You can move him around, but he's crap.
或許我可以安排幾個拳擊表演 賺個幾千塊
Maybe I can get a sparring gig for him, make a few hundred bucks.
住手
Stop.
這是我的機器人
It's my robot!
它花了我大半夜 辛苦的把它挖出來 他是我的
It took me half the night dragging him out of there. He's mine.
他是你的？但是用來修好他的零件是我的！
He's yours? Yeah. But the parts we're putting in him are mine!
你們二個白癡先不要吵 看看通電以后是什么樣子
You idiots should see if he powers up before you fight over him.
你怎么了？
What happened to you?
小心一點 退后
Watch out. Stay back.
看來它有一個映射功能 那是很罕見的
Looks like he's got a shadow function. That's pretty rare.
他可以模仿你的動作 記憶起來
He can mime your movements and store them in memory.
- 有沒有什么是我們可以利用的？- 我看是沒有
- Is there anything here we could use? - Not much.
哪里有個水桶...
There's a bucket...
有個我用來洗車的水桶
There's a bucket I use to wash the truck.
用來把它洗干凈 它聞起來像大便
Use it and clean him up. He smells like crap.
也把你自己洗一洗 你聞起來也像大便
Wash yourself off, too, while you're at it. You stink.
我把它調到最基本的無線功能
I switched him to remote. It's pretty basic.
用繩子拴住他 帶著他
Just use the toggles here to steer him and walk him.
- 你玩電動游戲 是吧？- 當然
- You play video games, right? - Of course.
一樣的概念 只是它是個一千磅的機器人
Same idea, only this one's a thousand-pound robot.
酷
Cool.
"Atom"
"Atom."
他的名字叫“ATOM” 我們可以讓他參加格斗嗎？
His name is Atom. Can we get him a fight?
他不是戰斗型的機器人
I don't think he was ever a boxing robot.
他是第二代的 2014年建造的 用來表演拳擊的
He's a G-2, built in early 2014. He was a sparring bot.
他們是建造來鏡像...
They must have built robots like this one
其他戰斗型的機器人
that could mirror the fighting style of any other robot.
好的 我們可以讓他參加格斗？
OK, so can we get him a fight?
你有沒有在聽？它是表演機器人
Are you not listening? He's a sparring bot.
它是可以承受很多撞擊 但是承受不了真正的大力一擊
Built to take a lot of hits, but never dishing out any real punishment.
你可以當成零件賣掉它
You could always sell him off for parts.
- 我們可不可以讓他參加格斗？- "你為什么要讓他參加格斗？"
- Can't you get him a fight? - "Why can't you get him a fight?"
天啊 你就是不放棄是吧？
God, you don't quit, do you?
你要我幫他放到格斗場 格斗祭 然后害死他？
You want me to put him in some bottom-rung scrap-fest to the death?
我看你在撞擊宮殿里面是那么害怕
I saw how scared you were at Crash Palace.
可以讓你參加格斗的地方會讓你嚇到尿褲子
The places that would let you fight this robot would make you pee your pants.
好極了 帶他去格斗
Excellent. Get him a fight.
頑固的孩子
Stubborn kid.
驚喜嗎？
Surprise, surprise.
我們散散步
Let's take a walk.
你聽得懂我說的嗎？
Can you understand me?
別擔心 我會保密的
Don't worry. Your secret's safe with me.
你認識Charlie非常久了
You've known Charlie a long time.
很久了 我們一起在健身房長大的
Too long. We both kind of grew up in this gym.
我父親是他的教練
My dad, he trained him.
那是他們 那是Charlie
That's them. That's Charlie.
- 他是什么樣子？- 當拳手的時候？
- What was he like? - As a boxer?
- 年輕的時候 - 他很不簡單
- As anything. - He was something.
他很瘦 強硬
He was lean, tough.
永不放棄 不會恐懼
No quit, no fear.
來這里 我讓你看看
Come here. I want to show you something.
給你看看2007年在鳳凰城的報導
I have this newspaper article from Phoenix 2007
當Charlie跟尼克康迪決戰的時候 那是他的巔峰
when Charlie fought Nico Tandy, the top contender.
你也有看那場拳賽？
You were at the Nico Tandy fight?
有的 Charlie本來只是熱身的對手 應該是很容易被揍扁的
I was. Charlie was supposed to be a warm-up fight, an easy win.
尼克本來是應該連汗都不流一滴的
Nico wasn't even supposed to break a sweat, but...
但是Charlie沒那么想 他一步一步的逼近尼克
nobody told Charlie that, so he just kept coming and coming at him.
結果你知道嗎？
Check this out.
這就是Charlie
That's Charlie.
一開始尼克不敢相信這個無名小卒會那么有膽識
First, Nico couldn't believe the balls on this nobody.
但是Charlie決不后退 尼克開始害怕了
But Charlie kept coming, and that's when Nico looked scared.
- 真的？- 是真的
- Really? - Really.
變成Charlie在玩弄尼克
He was toying with Nico.
這個世界排名第二名的拳手
The top contender, number two in the world,
Charlie像飛舞的蝴蝶玩弄著他
and Charlie was dancing with him.
Charlie整晚的腳步就像漂浮在拳擊臺上那么順
Charlie was floating inches off the canvas that night.
就像鬼魂一樣 尼克根本看不到他
He was like a ghost. Nico couldn't even see him.
我看得到
I could.
腳步是那么完美
He was beautiful.
就是那么完美
后來呢？Charlie擊敗尼克了？
So what happened? Did Charlie beat Nico Tandy?
不 尼克在第12回合揍扁了我 二次！
No, Nico Tandy put me on my ass in the 12th round. Twice.
第二次倒下 我被打暈了 再也站不起來！
Second time for good. Lights out.
當時計分板上 你是領先的！
You were ahead on the scorecards
- 一直到第12回合 - 結果第12回合 尼克擊倒我
- going into the 12th round. - Nico Tandy rung my bell
后面三年他都是世界拳王
and went on to be the undefeated world champ for the next three years.
- 他擊倒你？- 是的 還有很多人擊倒我
- He knocked you out? - Yeah. So did a lot of guys.
你也擊倒很多人啊！
You knocked a lot of guys out, too.
- 24 場19勝 大概是這樣 - 但是勝場都是擊倒勝
- 24 and 19. It's not exactly a career. - But every fight a knockout.
- 是的 - 贏或輸 沒有平手
- Yeah. - Win or lose, fight's not over
- 直到一方倒下 - 直到一方倒下
- till someone's on the mat. - Till someone's on the mat.
- 你父親教我的 - 沒錯 他教你的
- Your old man taught me that. - Damn straight he taught you that.
- 你還有跟誰比過？- 去收拾你的東西
- Who else did you fight? - Go get your stuff together.
我收好了 你有任何排名嗎？
I don't need to. Did you fight for the title?
你還要再收拾！我們再一個小時就出發了 去收拾！
Yeah, you do. We leave in an hour. Go.
哇 還你！
Wow. Here.
你留著吧
Keep it.
- 謝謝！ - 不客氣！
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
我喜歡Max
I like that kid.
他也喜歡你
He likes you.
- 我昨天晚上說的... - 不 一切盡在不言中
- What I said yesterday was... - No, nothing more to say.
我今天晚上會到亞特蘭大市
I'm heading off to Atlanta tonight
看看可不可以找到合伙人 募點錢 買個新的...
to see if I can get a partner or raise money to get a new bot.
這是你想要的吧 ？我走？
That's what you wanted, right? Me gone?
是啊 這是我想要的
Yeah, that's what I wanted.
好的
OK.
翻譯：閑閑的猛男 校對：目前沒有
“百麗來電”--拒接來電
趕快看
Look.
拳王在這里 宙斯在這里比賽
The champ is here. Zeus is here.
耶
Yeah.
沒有人能夠跟這個怪獸打二個回合
Zeus! No one has ever gone two rounds with this monster. Two rounds!
拳王交出他的冠軍腰帶 準備保衛戰
The champ puts his Real Steel world championship belt on the line tonight.
可能他今天晚上會遇到一場真正的較量
He just may have a real fight on his hands.
最后 還是宙斯贏了 最強的終極格斗機器人 晚安！
Zeus, greatest robot boxer of all time. Ever. End of story. Good night!
- 太酷了 真是太酷了 - 你說什么？
- So cool. It's so cool. - What?
來吧
Come on.
聽好 我要去找芬尼
Listen up. I got to go find Finn.
你要乖乖呆在這一區
I want you to stay in this area.
不要擋路 拳王來了 讓開路
Out of the way. Champ coming through. Zeus coming through.
走開走開 拳王要過來了
Move, move. Champ coming through.
法拉蘭蔻娃 宙斯是屬于他父親的
Farra Lemkova, daughter behind the father/daughter Zeus team.
大家說你父親只是出錢 你才是宙斯的領導者
They say your father's the money and you are the mind behind Zeus.
你太客氣了
You're very kind,
但是我要提醒你 松本先生才是宙斯真正的領導者！
but I assure you, the mind behind Zeus belongs to the great Tak Mashido.
是什么吸引了這個隱居的天才 這個天才神童
What did it take to lure the reclusive genius, former boy wonder
然后投入這個最重要的大賽的格斗機器人
and arguably the most important bot designer in the history of the sport
為什么有辦法讓他再出山？
out of retirement?
為什么你不自己問問他？
Why don't you ask him yourself?
宙斯是不是松本先生最偉大的設計？
Is this Tak Mashido's greatest creation?
宙斯是不斷的可以在戰斗中自主學習型的機器人
Zeus is autonomous and constantly evolving during a fight.
他有非常強的適應能力
With his adaptive operating system,
他可以隨時的辨識對手的戰斗模式 即時更新自己的模式
he recognizes patterns and rewrites his fight code instantaneously.
對于我及喬派克的理解 你是說宙斯......
For myself and Joe Sixpack out there, are you saying that Zeus?
我是說不管在場上發生什么事...
I'm saying that no matter what happens in that ring...
...結果都是一樣的
the result of any fight is inevitable.
宙斯只會...
What Zeus sees...
...神擋殺神 鬼擋殺鬼！
he kills.
太好了
Sweet.
我絕對不會投資你的生意
I'm never going into business with you.
我只需要一點小幫助
I just need a break here.
你不是還有一臺舊卡車 不是還有機器人在里面
You got that old bot truck out there. You always got something in there.
我有一個表演用的機器人 不值錢的
I got an old sparring bot, ain't worth the paint left on it.
我現在還能怎么辦？
What am I supposed to do with that?
帶他到動物園 動物園明天有比賽
The Zoo. Take him to the Zoo. They fight there tomorrow.
在動物園我只會被干掉
Even I wouldn't be caught dead at the Zoo.
我只需要借一點錢
I just need a little loan.
什么？
What?
- Charlie 你是認真的嗎？- 借一筆錢
- You're serious, Charlie? - A loan.
幾百 幾千 都可以 只要你愿意借
Couple hundred. Few hundred. Whatever you got.
我知道你有錢可以借給我
You know I'm good for it.
我很了解你 老兄 我很喜歡你的人
I know you, and as much as I like you, dude...
...只是 你實在是一個不會賭的人 兄弟
you're a bad bet, brother.
太好了 耶
Right, yeah.
你有沒有看到？艾克洛德只剩下那一半...
Did you see that? That's what's left of Axelrod.
你跑去哪里了？不是告訴你不要亂跑
Where you been? I told you to stay put.
你應該要看看宙斯 太神奇了！
You should have seen him. Zeus was, like, amazing!
- 神奇 阿？- 不敢相信 耶
- Amazing, huh? - Unbelievable, yeah.
他接二連三的打擊艾克洛德 很快的 太厲害了
He was just peppering Axelrod with punches, but so fast. It was incredible.
艾克洛德一拳也沒有打中宙斯 也撐不過一個回合
Axelrod didn't even land a punch. He didn't even survive the first round.
你以為拳擊就是這樣？
Is that what you think boxing is?
宙斯的比賽都是“安排”好的
Zeus beating up some piece of steel that they feed him?
艾克洛德只是一塊鐵 拳賽已經變得是那么低劣了
Axelrod's not just some piece of steel. And that is what boxing is now.
你連這個都不知道 我喜愛這個比賽 而且我還是圈內人
Deal with it. And I love it, and I'm in it now.
你還在圈內？你跟你的舊第二代機器人？
You're in it now, are you? You and your G-2 sparring bot?
他很厲害的 幫我們安排比賽 你就會知道
He's more than that. If you'd get us a fight, you'd see.
好的 你很幸運 有個地方叫做野獸園
You're in luck, kid. There's a lovely place called the Zoo.
明天下午 你可以參加格斗
Tomorrow afternoon, you'll get your fight.
- 很好 - 然后我們就徹底完蛋了
- Great. - And it will be the end.
我告訴你我不喜歡漢堡
I told you I hate hamburgers!
是墨西哥卷餅啦
It's a burrito!
右上勾拳
Right uppercut.
左上勾拳
Left uppercut.
蹲低一點 舉起你的雙手
Bend your knees. Rise up with both hands.
再來一次 蹲下 舉起你的雙手
Again. Bend your knees. Rise up with both hands.
你這樣一整晚？
You been up all night?
是的 我把它清理了一下
Yeah. I cleaned him up.
我用動作映射功能教他一點格斗技 然后同步到遙控器里面
I'm using shadow mode to program some fight moves and sync them to the remote.
是的 我看到你教他的雙上擊拳
Yeah. I saw that double-up punch you were showing him.
這是絕招
That's lethal stuff.
走吧 我們去格斗吧！
Let's do this.
吃早餐先吧
Let's do breakfast first.
你知道等下他就會被拆成碎片吧？
You know you're bringing him home in pieces, right?
等下你就知道
We'll see.
- 讓我來！ - Charlie肯頓 這是馬克思！
- Let me deal with this. - Charlie Kenton. This is Max.
首腦 叫我首腦
Kingpin. Call me Kingpin.
- 好吧！首腦 那么... - 一回合我們可以賺多少錢呢？
- All right, Kingpin, so... - How much a round?
我們正在巡回比賽
We on a field trip?
可以你可以跟我的機器人 Metro對打
All right. He can fight my robot Metro.
二分鐘 一回合 一百元
I'll give you a hundred bucks for one two-minute round.
- 接受它 - 三百
- Take it. - Three hundred.
一百元 小男孩 給你一百元是為了Metro練練
One hundred. Baby boy, I'm going to give you $100 just to get in with Metro.
何不500元打二個回合？
How about 500 for two rounds?
二個回合？小鬼 你的機器人連一個回合都撐不過
Two rounds. Son, he ain't going to survive one round.
- 如果它可以呢？- 它沒辦法的
- What if he does? - He ain't.
讓我們先假設它可以
Let's just say he does.
如果第一回合結束 他還能站著...
If he's still standing after one round...
...我就給你一千元
I'll give you a thousand bucks.
閉嘴！
Shut it!
但是如果他 我看是一定毀在那里 年輕人...
But if he dies in there, which he will, junior...
...剩下的零件都歸我了
I get to keep what's left.
一百元的賭注就好...
Take the hundred.
沒問題
Deal.
成局了 比賽開始！
We're on. We on!
走吧！
Let's go!
- 你應該接收100元的賭注的 - 我幫我們爭取更好的 1000元
- You should have taken the hundred. - I got us a thousand.
是啊 如果它贏得了
Yeah, if he wins.
你要我來操作嗎？
You want me to drive?
他是我的機器人 我自己操作！
He's my bot. I got this!
在這里的是真正的比賽 不是電動游戲
This ain't a video game. This is for real. Right here.
你不是說他會被拆碎？那誰操作有差嗎？
You said he's coming home in pieces. What difference does it make?
好吧！隨便你！
All right.
我來就好！
I got this.
開始吧 開始吧！
Let's get it on! Let's get it on!
讓我們像在香港打乒乓球那樣修理他吧！
Let's get it on like Ping-Pong in Hong Kong!
敲響鈴聲 敲鈴吧！
Give me a bell! Give me a bell!
不要看著Atom注意你的對手
Don't watch Atom. Watch your opponent.
注意他的腳 他要用腳釘住你
Watch out for that foot. He's looking to pin you.
我告訴你要小心那個踩腳的賤招數
I told you to watch for that foot plant. Come on.
注意！大榔頭要來了
Here comes the sledgehammer.
有沒有看到？
Did you see that?
- 來吧！ 控制他！ - 不要吼他 控制好他
- Come on! Get him! - Don't yell at him, control him.
滑到右邊 退后！
Slip right. Back step.
低頭
Duck.
- 不客氣 - 閉嘴！ 你在幫倒忙！
- You're welcome. - Shut up! You're not helping!
事實上 我認為我才對
Actually, I think I am.
后腦 你要快一點 移動快一點 屈膝
Backhand. You got speed on this guy. Just keep moving. Bob.
避開角落 不停移動 迂回前進
Slip out of that corner. Keep moving! Bob and weave!
就是這樣！總算聽懂我說的了
That's it! Now you're listening to me.
你的機器人真能挨揍 我告訴你 你的機器人很耐打
He can take a hit. I'll give you this. Your bot can take a hit.
你最好避開那個鎖頭 這個會對你是個大麻煩
You better slip that headlock. This ain't gonna end well for you.
我在躲！
I'm trying!
剩30秒！
Thirty seconds!
30... 半分鐘！
Thirty... Half a minute.
半分鐘！ 不停移動！ 不要停下來！
Half a minute! Keep moving! Just move!
只要再撐20秒
You've got 20 seconds!
- 再撐20秒就賺了1000元 讓我來操作！ - 不要！
That's a thousand bucks. Twenty seconds. Let me take over!
移動 然后 移動！
Move, then. Move!
不會吧！
Come on.
起來 Atom 站起來 Atom
Get up, Atom. Get up, Atom.
跟我一起數！ 跟我一起數！ 1！
Count with me! Count with me! One!
- 起來！ - 你知道你是在對一個機器說話吧？
- Get up! - You know you're talking to a machine?
4 5 6！
Four! Five! Six!
起來 Atom！
Get up, Atom!
站起來了！ 站起來了！
All the way up! All the way up!
耶！ 耶！
Yes! Yes!
我來搞定！
I'm going to fix it!
我來搞定 來吧！現在！
I'm going to fix it! Come on, now.
- 這里有一千元... - 耶 一千
- This thousand bucks... - Yeah, thousand.
全壓 壓他打不完第二回合！
Double or nothing he can't make another round.
- 耶 不用了 謝謝！ - 接受！全壓 再奧下去！
- Yeah, thanks anyway. - Deal. Double or nothing.
小男孩說了！ 再來！ 開始咯！
Baby boy said it! We're back on! We on!
你瘋了嗎？你剛剛丟了1000元？
Are you crazy? You threw away a thousand bucks!
他只是勉強支持住
He can barely stand up in there.
我真的很需要這筆錢
Look. I really need the money.
我知道 我來處理！
I know. Let's work.
天啊！
Jesus.
- 小心！踩腳賤招！ - 我看到了！
- Watch that. Watch that. - I got that.
- 我控制住了 - 它的系統崩潰了
- I got it. - That's a system failure!
- 失控了！ - 他要倒下了！
- I don't got it. - He's going down.
- 耶！ - 不！
- Yes! - No!
開始倒數！
Start the count!
1 2 3！
One! Two! Three!
4 5 6 7！
Four! Five! Six! Seven!
8 9！
Eight! Nine!
10！
Ten!
你辦到了！ 我們辦到了！哇！
You did it! We did it! Wow!
該走了 來吧 帶上你的機器人！
Time to go. Come on. Grab your robot.
我知道 我知道 我知道！
I know, I know! I know! I know!
首腦 付錢吧！
Kingpin, pay up.
好吧！好吧！好吧！我知道！我知道！
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know, I know, I know.
- 我們贏了！ - 走吧！趕快走！
- We owned! - Let's go. Come on, come on.
- 耶？- 我有沒有幫你安排過比賽？
- Yeah? - Have I got a fight for you.
一場比賽四千 如果贏了七千 周六晚上！
Saturday night. Guaranteed four grand. Seven if he wins.
四千？沒問題 我們走吧！
Four grand? You're on. Let's go!
翻譯：閑閑的猛男 校對：目前沒有
百麗 是我 Atom贏了
Bailey, it's me. He won.
你相信嗎？小鬼的機器人真的贏了！
Can you believe that? The kid's robot actually won.
我知道！
I know.
高興嗎？天啊！耶！
Happy? Oh, my God. Yeah.
Atom被揍了 被揍的很慘！
He's been bit. He's been bit real bad.
但是...
Anyway...
我只是希望讓你知道
I just wanted you to know.
刺拳 刺拳 勾拳！
Jab, jab, hook.
我認為你還要移動你的雙腿
I think you have to move your feet.
你的雙腿
Your feet. Feet.
漂亮的動作 小鬼！
Nice moves, kid.
你整晚沒有睡？
How long you been out here?
你看看！
Check it out.
我整晚沒睡做了一件了不起的事
I just spent the night doing something I think is amazing.
完全不可思議的事 然后搞定了
Incredibly amazing. If it works, you know?
- 你知道他的遙控器很臟了 - 是的
- You know his remote was spotty? - Yeah.
我丟掉了 不用了 我們不需要了！
I killed it. Got rid of it. We don't need it any more.
不會吧你？
How did you?
我想要重新再輸入！
I had to start over.
所以我用突擊者號的中心控制板
But I was able to use the spin frame from Ambush
然后把大聲公的聲控板移過去
and take the circuitry sleeve out of Noisy Boy,
成功了！
and it works.
他現在資料庫空了 但是更好用了！
He knows nothing, but it works. It really, really works.
什么更好用了？
What works?
讓我打開給你看！
I got to turn it on.
左刺拳 右上鉤拳！
Left jab, right uppercut!
日式！
Japan!
你把大聲公的聲控模式移植到Atom身上？
You put Noisy's voice recognition into Atom?
- 非常聰明 小鬼！ - 聰明？
- Pretty smart, kid. - Smart?
我是天才！
It could be genius!
那個是世界上最聰明的事
It could be the most incredible thing in the history of the entire world!
不要那么興奮 你把所有的汽水都喝完了？
Easy there, chief. Did you drink all these sodas?
我喝了一些 我需要你教Atom拳擊
I might have had a few. I need you to teach him to box.
你不要開玩笑了？他沒有那個級數去使出大聲公的組合動作
Are you kidding me? He's not advanced enough to handle Noisy's voice command.
所以他需要你的動作 你的組合
So he needs your moves. Your commands.
- 從腳步動作開始 - 別想了
- Start over from the ground up. - Forget it.
你曾經是一個拳擊手
You were a boxer.
昨天你在野獸園 可以清清楚楚的研判他們的動作
Yesterday at the Zoo, you could see things happen before they even happened.
我已經很久沒有打拳了 也不想再打了！
I haven't boxed in a long time. I'm not starting now.
- 那誰來教它打拳？- 你就教的不錯啊！
- Who's going to teach him to fight? - You're doing fine.
不需要我來教！對不起！
You don't need me. Sorry.
但是話說回來 那個舞步很酷
That was really cool, though, that dance.
我們周六晚上應該跳一下那個舞
You should do that on Saturday night.
- 不要取笑我 - 我是說真格的！
- Don't make fun of me. - I'm serious.
在比賽前 在你們進入場地的時候 你們應該跳的1
Before the fight, when you guys take the ring, you should do it.
我才不想在拳擊觀眾面前跳舞的
There's no way I'm dancing with a robot in front of a boxing crowd.
不會吧你？這一切都只是場秀！
Are you kidding me? This is just a show.
人們想看到一些從所未有的
People want to see something they've never seen.
你看 所有偉大的拳手！
Look. You think of all the greats.
像阿里 甜心雷 雷金王子 加瑪...
Think Ali, Sugar Ray, Prince Rakim, Gammer,
他們都有他們的措號
they all had their nicknames.
他們都有天分 特質...
They had their personae. They all had flair.
你呢？雖然你的機器人不起眼 但是如果你會跳舞 這就是你的特質
Now you? You might not have much robot, but with that dance, you got flair.
而且 你是小孩 人們總是喜歡小孩玩意的
Plus, you're a kid. People love that kid thing.
- 你幾歲？九歲？十歲？- 我十一歲了
- What are you? Like nine? Ten? - I'm 11.
你確定？
Are you sure you're 11?
是的 我確定我十一歲！
Yes. I'm sure I'm 11.
不管了 重點是人們想看到這個
Anyway, the point is people want to see that.
你不是故意搞我吧？
You're really not messing with me?
我沒搞你 觀眾會喜歡這個的！
I am not messing with you. They're going to love it.
- 酷 - 但是...
- Cool. - But...
- 什么？- 你也要幫我
- What? - I won't do it unless you help me.
你要我一起跳 我不跳 你就不跳？
I can't dance. You're on your own there.
不是 是教拳擊
No. Boxing.
- 噢 我懂了！ - 我來編程序
- Oh, I see. - I program the robot.
- 你來教他拳擊 - 然后你跳舞
- You teach him to box. - And you dance.
然后你來跳舞！
And you dance.
- 好嗎？- 好！
- Yeah. - Yeah?
一言為定
Deal.
那樣會很酷的
It's going to be cool.
很好
Nice.
你的對手都是比較高的 所以你要打高一點！
You're going to be punching guys bigger. You're going to have to punch up.
對了 就是這樣！
That's it.
很好！
Nice.
你也是老骨頭一把了？
You, too, old man?
來吧！讓我們好好鍛煉！
Come on. Let's get to work.
很好 再做一次
Nice! Let's do that again.
很好！三連擊組合！
Nice. Three-punch combo.
組合拳！
Combo.
再一次 再一次！
Again. Again.
快一點 再快一點 很好！
Faster. Faster. Nice.
你甚至不用調呼吸 很好 我喜歡！
You're not even out of breath. I like it.
讓我們看看你的動作！
Let's see how you move.
很好
That's good.
退后幾步！ 左勾拳 左勾拳！
Step around! Left hook! Left hook!
就是這樣 每次都是
That's it. Every time.
上勾拳
Upper cut!
很好的比賽 各位
Great fight, fellas.
1055頻率 WRUT 家庭衛星機器人格斗頻道
105.5, WRUT, the satellite home of robot boxing.
第二個扣應 你有什么要分享的？
Caller two, what do you got for me?
你有沒有聽過一個小個頭的機器人 叫做Atom的？
Have you heard about this little bot out there, his name is Atom?
噢 是的
Oh, yeah.
我們一群朋友昨天晚上有看到 他會跳舞
My buddies and I saw him the other night, and he dances.
- 你是說 "舞蹈"？- 是的 就是舞蹈
- Did you say "dances"? - You heard me.
他在比賽前都會跟個小男孩一起表演舞蹈
He dances pre-fight with this little kid,
觀眾都看瘋了 樂瘋了！
and the crowd went nuts for these two.
先不討論哪些花招小玩意
You put the gimmick aside for a second,
我手里有份他打敗的人的名單
and I'm holding here a list of the bots he's beaten.
趙 華爾街 獨眼Jack 一個個都是不好惹的是吧！
Chaos. Wall Street. One-Eyed Jack. No slouches on that list, right?
Atom把它們統統打敗了
Atom's fought them all, beat them all.
Atom很快 他躲過這些大家伙的絕招 不可思議是吧！
This bot is fast! He escapes shots from these bigger bots, it's insane!
不用懷疑 聽眾們一定會記得這個名字
No doubt. I'm telling you, listeners, remember this name:
Atom 沒錯 A-T-O-M 這個機器人值得一看
Atom. That's right, A-T-O-M. This bot is one to watch.
- 很好的格斗 先生 - 謝謝！謝謝！
- Awesome fight, sir. - Thanks, thanks.
好比賽！
Great fight.
- 你們的表演很精彩 - 謝謝！
- You guys put on a good show. - Thanks.
我們想邀請你們參加我們的比賽
We'd like to invite you to fight on our card,
維吉尼亞州 史倍壯中心 底特律 周五晚上
Virgin America Spectrum Detroit, Friday night.
好的 那是WRB...這不是職業比賽？
Right. That's a WRB... That's a League fight.
沒錯 你怎么說 老弟 你準備好了嗎？
Damn right it is. What do you say, fellas? You ready for the show?
當然 耶
Heck, yeah.
這是不計名次的 但是還是職業級的
It's the undercard, but it's still a League fight.
我要你放松一點 平常心
I just want you to be relaxed. I want you to be relaxed.
不要祛場 不要給我那個疑惑的表情
No freaking out. Don't get all freaky-deaky on me.
如果你疑惑了 你會被修理的很慘
You go freaky-deaky, this whole thing can go south.
不管怎么樣 享受比賽 享受樂趣 不要緊張
Whatever you do, have fun, have fun. You got to have fun, you understand me?
我們來到這里已經很不容易的 祛場會搞砸一切的
We've come too far to get out there and freak out and blow this whole thing.
一切會很有趣的 千萬不要祛場！
We're going to have fun, and we're going to not freak out!
我們好好地放松心情 好好的修理對手一頓
We're going to stay loose, and we're just going to bam him.
這是我一輩子的夢想 我們將要參加...
I've spent my whole life waiting to get here. We're going to...
告訴你 相信我 千萬不要祛場 聽到了嗎？
I tell you what. Trust me when I say no freaking out. You got it?
- 聽到了 - 很好
- I got it. - Good.
你們被邀請到連科娃貴賓室 請跟我來
You have been invited to Lemkova Suite. Follow me, please.
你說什么？再說一遍
What was that? One more time.
連科娃貴賓室 宙斯的貴賓室
Lemkova Suite. Zeus Suite.
當然 讓我們一起到拳王的貴賓室
Sure. Yeah. Let's head up to the champ's suite. Sure.
哇
Wow.
- 先生們 我是法羅 蘭蔻娃 - 你好 我是Charlie肯頓 這是...
- Gentlemen, I'm Farra Lemkova. - Yeah. I'm Charlie Kenton, and...
當然還有松本先生
And this, of course, is Tak Mashido.
老天爺！是松本先生
Holy shit. It's Tak Mashido.
我知道你們今晚有一場重要的比賽 所以我就直接了當說了
I know you have a very important fight tonight, so I'll get right to it.
那個動作我喜歡 很漂亮的動作 所以... (Charlie已經語無倫次了）
It's a little far from the action for my liking. It's nice. I like it, though.
漂亮的相片... 哇！非常漂亮
Very nicely... Wow. That's a great shot.
看看這個 你要個簽名嗎？你介意嗎？
Look at that. You want an autograph? Would you mind?
我想買你們的機器人
I'd like to buy your robot.
他對我們是一個很好的前場表演機器人 所以我愿意付你們
He'd be useful sparring bot for Zeus. And for that I'm willing to pay.
二十萬
$200,000.
- 沒問題 - 我不要賣
- Done. - He's not for sale.
- 當然要 我們絕對可以... - Atom是不賣的
- Of course he is. We can definitely... - He's not for sale.
你們還有十五分鐘要對上雙子星
You are 15 minutes away from getting in the ring with Twin Cities,
一個邪惡的職業機器人
a vicious League bot.
所以我的報價在鈴聲前才有效
So, to be clear, my offer stands until the starting bell.
好的 但是讓我再說一遍 不賣！
OK. And just to be clear, he's not for sale!
現在不賣 以后也不賣
Not now, not ever.
給我一分鐘想清楚 好嗎！
Give me a minute to clear this up, OK?
松本 你好嗎？Max！！慢一點！
Tak, how are you? Max!
聰明一點 我知道你很喜歡他
Be smart. I know you love him,
但是過二十分鐘 它可能就毀了
but in 20 minutes there may be nothing left to love.
- 考慮一下 接受吧！ - 你動動頭腦想一下
- Think about it. Take the offer. - You think about it.
他們為什么要賣Atom？因為他是與眾不同的
Why does she want Atom? Because he's different from other bots!
是啊 是不一樣 是小個 虛弱的
Yeah, he's different. He's smaller, weaker,
- 而且他會被揍的很慘的 - 他是拳擊手
- and he's going to get his ass kicked. - He's a boxer.
我們叫他拳擊 你教他拳擊
We taught him to box. You taught him to box!
- 這個就是它的價值 - 我也是這么認為
- That's worth something. - I think it is, too.
我想這個值20萬 20萬大元
I think it's worth 200 grand. Two hundred grand.
我們可以整晚都在這里兜
We can go round and round this all night long.
看著我
Look at me.
但是絕對不會賣的
But it's not going to happen.
對不起我還有比賽
I got a fight to get to.
各位先生女士們 今晚...
Ladies and gentlemen, tonight,
即將帶來的 鋼鐵擂臺冠軍杯
the march towards the Real Steel Championship
來到了底特律
makes its way through Detroit's
維吉尼亞州 史倍狀中心
Virgin America Spectrum!
開始我們的第一輪排名賽
Kicking off the evening, in our first undercard,
二個頭的暴君
the two-headed tyrant,
雙子星
Twin Cities!
對手是第一次參加職業比賽的
Opposing Twin Cities, in his first professional fight,
讓我們一起喊
hailing from parts unknown,
Atom
Atom!
- 跳得好 老板 - 謝謝
- Nice work, boss. - Thanks.
- 你切換到戰斗模式了？- 當然
- Did you switch him to fight mode? - Of course.
- 雙子星是訓練來撕裂對手 - Atom 也可以
- This bot is tough to put down. - Atom can do it.
看看那里 那二個握著搖桿在熒幕后面的怪胎
Look over there. You see those geeks with the joysticks and consoles?
他們完全控制他們的機器人
They're controlling everything their bot does.
他們隨時監看它的系統
They're monitoring his systems,
隨時調整他的戰術
seeing what he sees, stadium feeds of the fights.
這個不是以前我們對戰的地下那種用遙控器的級別
This is not like the underground handheld remote bots
這是職業賽 你要了解到
we've been fighting. This is the League. Stand on that.
那我們要怎么做？
So what do we do?
我們要聰明一點 有耐心 然后祈禱
We fight smart, we be patient. And pray.
正經一點 不是那種祈禱
Seriously, pray.
準備好！
Ready!
- 準備好了 - 手舉起來
- Ready! - Hands up.
拳手準備好了！ 開始！
Fighters ready! Fight!
交戰開始
Engage.
滑動！ 右邊！ 退后 右 左 左 掩護好
Slip! Right! Lean back. Right, left! Cover up!
低頭 左勾拳
Duck! Left roundhouse!
該死的
Damn it.
閃左邊！ 閃右邊！防守好！
Lean left! Lean right! Cover up! Cover up!
- 發生什么事了？- 他要對上太多頭了
- What's going on in there? - He's taking too many hits.
把手舉起來
Get your hands up!
離開角落！ 移動！
Get out of that corner! Move!
他在被狠狠修理了 趕快告訴他怎么做！
He's getting killed in there! Tell him what to do!
對手有二個頭 二個頭都對著我們 而且沒有盲點
That guy's got two heads, a foot of reach on us, and no blind spot.
對手一定有弱點 找出來吧！
He's got to have a weakness. Find it!
看到了 等一下 看到了！
Wait, wait, wait.
右手肩膀 右手肩膀 他有一個習慣動作
Right shoulder, right shoulder, right shoulder! He's got a tell!
每次出右拳的時候 他都有一個準備動作
He's got a hitch in his shoulder every time he throws that right bomb!
抓到了 看到沒？又有準備動作了
We got him! See? Here it comes again!
低頭！ 旋轉！ 滑到左邊！ 繞一圈！ 一 二！
Duck! Spin! Slide left! Roundhouse! One, two!
退后 退后一步 滑到左邊！
Backstep. Backstep. Backstep. Lean right.
來吧 Charlie 跟上去！
Come on, Charlie! Get in there!
我們要縮近到對我們有利的距離
Got to get in close where he can't use that size and reach on us!
攻擊左邊身體 右邊身體 再左邊身體
Left to the body! Right to the body! Left to the body!
耶 有作用了！
Yeah, it's working!
繼續低一點的姿勢 左 右 左
Stay downstairs! Left, right, left!
- 這個模式沒有用 - 左 右勾 滑動
- These program modes aren't working. - Left! Right hook, slip!
右上鉤拳！ 左上鉤全！躲左邊 閃右邊
Right uppercut! Left uppercut! Duck left. Counter right!
- 打到他 Atom！ - 看看Charlie的絕招
- Get him, Atom! - Here comes the Charlie Special.
三連擊攻擊身體！ 外面！ 里面！ 反向！
Three-punch combo to the body! Out! In! Counter!
- 一二一連擊！ - 一二一連擊！
- Two-one-two! - Two-one-two.
盯住他 ！ 前后分身 ！
Stay on him! Lunging right!
你要讓他逃走右拳攻擊身體！ 右直拳打頭！
Don't let him go. Right to the body! Straight right to the head!
系統崩潰了！
We got a systems crash!
打倒他 Atom！
Get him, Atom!
怎么可能發生這種事？
This is not happening, man.
- 打倒他 Charlie！ - 左旋轉
- Put him away, Charlie! - Spin left!
右旋轉
Spin right!
干掉他
Finish him!
- 就是現在 - 右勾拳
- Do it! - Right uppercut!
倒了！
He's down!
1！2！3！
One! Two! Three!
4！5！6！
Four! Five! Six!
我們干掉他了 準備好！
We got him. Stay down!
結束比賽 擊倒！
He's out! He's out!
耶！
Yeah!
回來！
Corner!
回到角落來！
Corner! Corner.
勝利！
Victory!
在一分47秒...
In a time of one minute, 47 seconds
第一回合......
of the first round,
Atom擊敗了...
Atom has defeat...
感謝各位今天晚上的觀看
I want to thank everyone for coming out tonight!
我們從垃圾場來的的小巨人 擊倒了職業級的機器人
Our little bot from the junkyard got a shot at a League fight.
爽不爽？
How about that?
最后我要對一個背地里操作的女孩說...
And the last thing I want to say to a special girl who won't be named,
法羅 蘭蔻娃
Farra Lemkova.
她想買我的機器人 用你們的錢來操作比賽
That instead of buying my robot, using your money to control this sport...
- 就是她 - 不是我說的
- That's it! - I'm not done.
你為什么不給小巨人一個最大的機會？
Why not give the littlest guy the biggest shot?
因為我敢打賭 你不敢給我們這個機會
Because I bet if you give him a shot, he'll surprise you!
大家想不想看小巨人
Wouldn't you like to see a little guy
對抗聯盟冠軍
get a shot at the Real Steel Championship?
我要挑戰宙斯！
I challenge Zeus to a fight.
任何時間 任何地點！
Any time, any place, anywhere!
告訴我們 ！ 我們就來！
You name it! We will be there!
我來為各位安排這場比賽
I'm going to get us that fight!
Atom Atom Atom...
Atom, Atom, Atom...
那是很沒腦的舉動 你就這樣挑戰宙斯？
That was a ballsy move, you challenging Zeus like that.
那只是一時的沖動
That's one thing to call it.
很多人會很想看的
A lot of people would like to see that.
- 是的 大家都想 - 聽這個小鬼說的 天啊！
- You're damn right they would. - You listening to this kid? Jeez!
- 好比賽 兄弟 - 謝謝你
- Good fight, fellas. - Thanks, man.
- 看看這個 慶祝一下 - 耶
- Look at this. Let's celebrate. - Yeah.
- 好吧 7-3分賬 對不對？- 耶 我7你3
- All right, 70-30, right? - Yeah, 70 for me and 30 for you.
- 對對對 - 很好笑！
- That's so right. - That's very funny.
- 我就說我們不應該賣掉它 - 喔 喔 喔！
- I told you we shouldn't have sold him. - OK. No, no, no.
我想起來了 誰才對？說啊 說出來“Max是對的”？
I remember now. Who's right? Say who's right. Say "Max is right."
好啦好啦 你才是對的！
All right, all right. All right.
- 我們合作無間是吧 - 不是不是 要說“Max是對的”
- We're a good team. - No, no. Max is right.
不敢相信 這么多錢 感謝你 雙子星！
That was unbelievable. Thank you, Twin Cities.
- 收好了？- 耶
- We set? - Yeah.
- 我們去慶祝了！ - Charlie男孩
- Let's do it. - Charlie boy.
- 里奇 我才正想要打給你 - 噢？是嗎？
- Ricky, I was just going to call you. - Oh, yeah.
我是真的打算打給你
I actually really was going to call you.
沒事 不用在意
Don't worry about that.
真的是了不起的比賽！
That was a heck of a fight.
恭喜二位 真的是太好了！
Congratulations to both of you. That was good.
真的是了不起的戰斗 干得好 小朋友
It was an amazing fight. That was a great job, young man.
- 來吧！兄弟 - 干嘛？
- Come on, man. - What?
- 你不會是說真的吧？- 你以為我在開玩笑？
- You serious? - You thought I was joking
我說“見你一次就海扁你一次”
when I said I'd beat you within an inch of your life?
你以為我是開玩笑？告訴你 絕對不是！
He thought that was a joke. It wasn't a joke.
我小孩在這里 我也準備錢要給你了 不要這樣
I got a kid here. And I have your money. We don't have a problem.
我看你也不敢
I'm sure you do,
但是不只是因為錢是吧？你都知道的
but I think we know it's about much more than money, don't we?
好的 你要多少？二萬 二萬五 三萬夠不夠？
All right. What do you want? You want 25, 30? You want 30 grand?
- 我手頭上有現金 - 是哦！對啊
- I got the money in cash here. - Yeah, right.
趕快跑！Max 跑 快跑！
Let's go! Max, go! Go, go! Run!
- 趕快跑 跟上 快！ - 趕快抓住他！
- Run! Come on. Keep up, keep up! - Get him now!
跑 快！
Run! Come on!
放開他！放開他！
Get off him! Get off him!
過來！
Come here!
嗨 里奇！
Hey, Ricky.
那是他的錢 跟他無關
That's his money! Leave him out of this!
停
Stop!
停！
把所有的錢都拿走 全拿走！
Take all his money. Take it all.
小朋友 你的朋友是個人渣
Your friend's a real dirt bag, kid.
他是我父親
He's my father!
看來可以少扁你一次了
Well. Looks like a little less than an inch of your life.
嗯 好好的給你上一課
Well, buddy, that will teach him.
就像以前一樣 Charlie男孩
Just like old times, Charlie boy!
走吧 兄弟們
Let's go, boys.
對不起 Max 我很抱歉
I'm sorry, Max. I'm sorry. Sorry.
- 我們來這里做什么？- Max 只是...
- What are we doing here? - Max, just...
來找法羅？她是不是打給你了？我們要跟宙斯比賽了？
Is it Farra? She called you, didn't she? We're going to get the Zeus fight.
不是宙斯 我想了很多 然后......
It's not the Zeus people. I've been thinking about all this, and...
Max
Max!
很高興見到你
It's so good to see you.
- 為什么她在這里？- 你最好還是現在跟她回去
- What is she doing here? - It's better if you go with her now.
我們被痛扁了 所以你打電話給她來接我？
We get beat up, so you call her to come and get me?
他被打了 我就說他沒法照顧好Max的！
He's been beat up. I told you he couldn't take care of him!
是的 我打給他們 你看我們 真是一團糟
Yeah. I called her. Look at us. We're a mess.
我們很好 叫他們走
We're fine. She can leave!
Atom打得很好 我們可以把錢再賺回來
Atom's fighting good. We can make the money back.
Charlie 拜托！
Charlie, please.
只是...
Just...
Charlie 我們過得很好
Charlie, we're doing so good.
Charlie 拜托 不要
Charlie, please, no.
不要 不要 不要
Don't. Don't. Don't.
拜托 拜托
Please. Please.
相信我 這樣對你比較好 好嗎？
Trust me, kid. It's better this way, all right?
你以為這樣對我比較好 其實不是的
I know you think you know what's right, but you don't.
你還年輕 你不懂
You're too young. You don't know.
看著我 相信我！
Look at me, trust me.
而且法律上 她有你的監護權 我還能怎么做？
And legally she has custody, so what can I do?
我還能做什么？
What can I do?
我不要你的錢 馬文
I don't want your money, Marvin.
Max 我們有自己的游泳池哦
Max, we have our own swimming pool
而且我們有按摩浴缸 還有很多好玩的玩具給你玩
and we have a hot tub and a lot of super fun toys to play with.
你要玩玩嘛？很好玩的哦
Do you want to play with them? It's going to be fun.
情況如何？
What's going on?
謝謝你 他根本不跟我講話
He won't even talk to me, so thanks for that, Charlie.
我先到車子里面等
I'm going to wait in the car.
你不想講話？好 我說
You don't want to talk, fine. I'll talk.
你要我說什么？我很抱歉？
What do you want me to say? I'm sorry?
從一開始就是這樣
You knew from day one what this was.
從你開始決定上車就是這樣
You decided to take the ride.
你以為我可以跟你那個破爛堆撿到...
You thought me, you, and a little robot from the junk heap
的破機器人一起坐著看夕陽？
were going to ride off into the sunset?
你看錯我了
No, you forgot who I was!
你應該過的好一點的生活...
You deserve better...
...比我還好
than me.
拜托說幾句話吧？
Will you say something, please?
我努力過了 你還要我怎么做？
I tried. What do you want from me?
我要你為我奮斗
I want you to fight for me.
這就是我想要的
That's all I ever wanted.
翻譯：閑閑的猛男 校對：目前沒有
不要問
Don't ask.
Max走了？
So no Max.
最好的安排 馬文及黛博拉他們有錢 會好好照顧Max
It's better this way. Marv and Debra have money. Max is set.
你有沒有看到他看你的樣子？
Did you not see the way he looked at you?
就像我看我爹的樣子
That's the way I looked at my dad.
我多想再重溫那種感覺
Even now I would give anything to have that back.
你父親不一樣 他從一開始就跟你在一起
Your dad was special. He was in your corner from day one.
我 我早就搞砸了
Me, come on. I blew it.
我搞砸了
I blew it.
當Max出生的時候...
When Max was born I just...
...我嚇傻了
freaked out.
你沒有感到滿足嗎？
But something would have been better than nothing.
不對 是手足無措
I wouldn't know where to start.
- 我不滿足 - 不 你很幸福
- Yeah, you do. - I don't.
- 你是的 - 不是
- You do. - No.
你是的
You do.
我要走了
I got to go.
開了1200英里就為了這個吻？
Twelve hundred miles for a kiss.
值得 值得！
Worth it. Worth it.
去找他 Charlie！
Go get him, Charlie.
你說得好像你爹的口氣
You sound like your dad.
我知道你認為我遺棄了你
Look, I know you think I abandoned you,
而且我還真的這樣做了
and I guess I did originally.
你還賣掉我
Then you sold me.
Charlie？
Charlie.
這個地方一點都不歡迎你
You have no business being here.
沒錯 你有全部的監護權 他是你的
That's true. You've got full custody. He's yours.
而且我知道所有的事都是我的錯 但是請你讓我...
And I know I've done all kinds of wrong by this kid, but if you'll let me...
...我想要做一些補償
I'd just like to do one thing right.
好的
Right.
- 講到哪里了？- 你賣掉我
- Where were we? - You sold me.
哦 對了 耶 沒錯
Right, yeah, that happened.
- 等一下 什么？- 然后我們被痛扁一頓
- Wait, what? - Then we had our asses kicked.
然后你還要睡在一個破卡車里面
And you slept on a shelf in a truck, and it was awful.
- 很危險 - 非常危險
- And dangerous. - Really dangerous.
我知道 天啊 我真的很對不起你
I mean, I know. God. I'm sorry.
你來就是要說這個？就是要說你很抱歉？
That's why you came? To say you're sorry?
不 不止這些
No. I mean, yes. Yes.
我來還要再說 我了解了
But no. No, I came to tell you that I heard you.
我懂了 雖然我有一點遲鈍 但是我懂了
I got it. I'm a little slow, but I got it.
我知道我去流浪了 當你出生的時候
I know you had a bum ride, and I wasn't there and I should have been.
我實在不應該去的
I should have been.
你媽媽真的是...
Your mom was...
她很好是吧 很酷吧？
She was cool, wasn't she?
是的
She was.
她是最好的
She was the coolest.
耶 是的
Yeah, she was.
對她的事 我也很遺憾
And I'm sorry about... what happened with her.
馬克思 我沒法讓時間倒流
And I can't get those years back, Max,
但是現在我來了...
but I'm here right now...
...就像你看到的 我已經準備好要為你戰斗
and if you're up for it, I'm ready to fight.
跟宙斯的比賽安排好了
We got the Zeus fight.
真的？
What?
沒錯 安排好了
No, no, we didn't.
準備跟宙斯戰斗
You got the Zeus fight.
黛博拉 可以請你通融嗎？
So what do you say, Debra?
可不可以讓我們在一起奮戰 最后一次？
Can we do this one last thing?
- 就一晚 - 我們就這個小小要求
- One night. - It's all we need. Thank you.
我們很可能被痛宰 但是至少我們在一起奮斗
We'll probably get our asses kicked, but at least we'll go down swinging.
耶？你怎么決定？
Yeah? What do you say?
歡迎來到紐約的濱中心及觀看鋼鐵擂臺冠軍大賽
Welcome to New York's Bing Arena and the Real Steel Championship Bout.
提姆 這是場我們不敢想象會安排的比賽
Tim, it's the fight we never thought we'd see.
宙斯 永遠不敗的WRB拳王
Zeus, the undefeated WRB champion,
迎戰最近新崛起的初級的Atom
against the underdog, rising star Atom.
拳王的老板答應了這場比賽
The champ's handlers have agreed to fight
打破了聯盟循環賽的規則
outside the circle of well-known League bots,
而且準備給觀眾一場真正的重量級的對抗
and have decided to give the people a true David versus Goliath spectacle.
提姆 告訴我 拳王是不是腦袋進水了？
Now, Tim, help me out on this. Has the Zeus camp lost their mind?
有史以來最偉大的機器人格斗拳王
The greatest robot boxer of all time
為了跟一個第二代的 Atom 戰斗而交出他的腰帶？
gives a shot at the belt to a G-2 named Atom?
赫伯 如果你問松本先生 宙斯團隊是不是瘋了
Well, Herb, if you ask Tak Mashido, Team Zeus has lost their minds.
他可能會用一貫冷酷的表情回你
Now, he may look cool as he enters the arena,
然后用輕蔑的表情看待這場比賽
but he has made no bones about his disdain for this match up.
前幾天我們的攝影機試著要補抓這號表情
Our cameras tried to catch up with him earlier this week.
看看這個片段 松本先生甚至根本不想停下來跟媒體講話
Look at this clip. Mashido wouldn't even stop to talk to the press,
好像這場比賽是是侮辱了他偉大的創造物
referring only to this fight as an insult to his creation.
Charlie Atom的教練做的已經不只是跳級挑戰宙斯
Now, Max Kenton, Atom's trainer, did more than just challenge Zeus.
還是公開的挑戰
He did so publicly.
這個挑戰對拳王的公關形象是一個大挑戰
The challenge went viral and created a PR nightmare for the champ.
沒有任何合約 但是我相信拳王的團隊很清楚他們在做什么
No argument there. And I think the Zeus camp knows exactly what they're doing.
那就是他們做的 來吧
That they do. Come on.
給一個無名小卒一個機會來挑戰
Giving a shot at the belt to a nobody from nowhere.
那個垃圾廠的挑戰者？這一切都只是噱頭罷了
This "junkyard dog," if you will. That's a marketing stunt.
而且從觀眾的反應看起來 很奏效！
And judging from this crowd, that stunt is working.
我們贏不了 是吧？
We can't win, can we?
很難說
We'll see.
挑戰者正慢慢的走到他的角落
As the challenger makes his way into the arena,
你可以感受到激情的洶涌
you can hear the surge of excitement.
Atom已經抵達WRB的比賽現場
Atom has arrived onto the WRB scene with a vengeance,
用他“像人類”的外觀
using a style, some would call it human-like,
他戰斗的模式是非常少見的
that bot fighting has rarely seen.
Atom 跟他的迷你訓練員已經踏上比賽場地
Atom and his pint-size trainer step into the ring
看看法羅的表情 說明了一切
and the look on Farra Lemkova's face says it all.
歡迎來到大聯盟 年輕人
Welcome to the bigs, junior!
現在的賭盤開出來是1賠5 賭Atom撐不過第一回合
I'm giving one-to-five odds that Atom don't make it out the first round.
有人要賭嗎？
Who wants some?
現在可以開始下注了
I'll take some of that action.
嗨 我要下注
Hey, there! I'll take some of that action.
最近如何... 伙伴？
How's it going... partner?
誰是你的伙伴？
Partner?
很好 我下十萬 怎么樣？刺不刺激？
That's great. How about a hundred K? Is that funny?
十萬？賭Atom 撐不過第一回合？
Hundred K says Atom doesn't see round two.
你有帶那么多現金？
You carrying around that kind of scratch?
- 耶 - 十萬？
- Yeah. - Hundred K?
記得 我在101區 C 排
Tell you what. Remember section 101, row C,
然后把我的錢拿過來
and you can bring me my money right to my seat.
101 C排 ？十萬 ？
101, row C? Hundred K?
你聽到的 “宅男”！
You heard me, homey.
-宅男 ？- 是的 ？
- Homey? - Right?
宅在家里的大男孩
Homeboy!
沒事 保鏢們 酷！
All right. Peace out, posse.
來吧甜心 我們走吧
Come on, sugar. Let's go.
- 永遠不敗的 - 表演時間
- Never beaten. - It's showtime!
永不恐懼的
Never threatened.
拳擊場上的王者
The king of the ring,
機器人的統治者
the ruler of robots!
歡迎我們王者宙斯！
Bow down to the mighty Zeus!
哦！shit ！
Oh, shit!
好屌！
That was awesome.
來吧 我們走
Come on, let's go.
各位先生女士們
Ladies and gentlemen,
在五回合的拳擊規則下
in a bout scheduled for five rounds
進行世界拳擊冠軍大賽
for the World Robot Boxing Championship,
在我右手邊的是 挑戰者Atom
in the corner to my right, the challenger, Atom!
表現一下
Showboat!
以及 在我左邊的是...
And in the corner to my left,
整個宇宙最偉大的......
the undeniable champion of this universe
以及所有宇宙最厲害的...
and any other universe known or unknown,
宙斯王者
the mighty Zeus!
現在 各位先生女士們準備好
And now, ladies and gentlemen, are you ready
鋼鐵擂臺
for Real Steel!
就是我們期待已久的！
This is what it's all about!
鈴聲響起 馬上開始比賽了
There's the starting bell and we are underway.
機器人慢慢的離開他們的角落
The bots emerge from their corners.
宙斯一下就把Atom打趴 Atom已經倒下了
Zeus decks Atom, and he is already down.
站起來！
On your feet!
看來又是一出宙斯式的慘劇
Looks like we are in for another Zeus clinic.
裁判馬特蓋格已經出來開始倒數了
Referee Matt Geiger coming in the ring to start the count.
站起來！
Get up!
用手撐起來！站起來！
Push up! Stand up!
但是看看 小巨人已經站起來了
But look at this. The little bot's back on his feet
準備迎接宙斯的第二輪猛攻
to get a second blistering attack from Zeus!
不到十秒時間 Atom又一次倒下了
Atom is down for the second time in less than ten seconds.
- 太強了 - 好樣的 那才像我的人！
- He's too strong! - That's my boy right there!
站起來繼續比賽
Get up and get in the game!
來吧！ 不 拜托 Atom 站起來！
Come on! No, please Atom, get up! Please!
站起來！ 站起來！ 站起來！
Get up! Get up! Get up!
又一次 挑戰者站了起來！
Once again, the challenger finds his feet!
低頭 后退！
Lean back!
Atom被連續擊逼到了繩索邊上
Atom's getting pummeled into the corner!
- 離開角落！ - 移動！
- Get out of there! - Move!
一陣摧毀式的近身攻擊
A demolishing inside shot.
把手舉起來！
Get your hands up!
舉起來！
Hands up!
揍扁那個罐頭
Crush that little can!
離開角落
Get out of the corner!
肯頓絕望的命令他的機器人離開死亡的角落
Kenton desperately trying to command his robot out of that suicide corner.
蹲低一點！
Get your feet under you!
晚安 表演機器人！
Good night, sparring bot!
今晚只是時間長了一點 但是宙斯又一次要擊倒了...
It might have taken Zeus a bit longer, but he's done it again!
Atom第三次倒下了 也可能是今晚最后一次倒下
Atom is down for the third and possibly final time tonight.
- 站起來！ - 2！
- Stand up! - Two!
3！
Three!
Atom 站起來！
Atom, get up!
- 起來 Atom - 起來 Atom
- Get up, Atom. - Get up, Atom.
- 6 ！7！ - 起來！
- Six! Seven! - Get up!
8！ 9！
Eight! Nine!
真不敢相信！似曾相識 小巨人又一次站了起來
I don't believe this! Against all odds, this little bot is on his feet again.
來吧 Atom！
Come on, Atom!
它撐不下去的
He can't survive this!
- 來吧 Charlie！ - 右上勾拳
- Come on, Charlie! - Right uppercut!
Atom 使出一記絕招！
Atom has landed a punch!
宙斯被出乎意料的上鉤拳擊中 搖晃的退后
Zeus is stunned as he reels back from an uppercut that he never saw coming!
前進！
Advance!
退一步 出右拳！
Fade back, counter right!
右交叉拳！ 右交叉拳！ 右交叉拳！ 左勾拳！
Right cross! Right cross! Right cross! Left hook!
- 來吧！ 上吧！ - 擊倒他！
- Let's go! Come on! - Take him down!
第一次 Atom占了優勢
For the first time in his dominant run,
宙斯第一次遇到一個打不退的對手
Zeus has met a bot who simply won't back down!
群眾已經瘋狂了 宙斯使出渾身解數
The crowd is going nuts! Zeus gives it everything he's got
第一回合已經剩下15秒鐘了
as we reach the last 15 seconds of round one!
宙斯把Atom逼到角落 使出雙組合拳
Zeus corners Atom, going double duty with both fists!
上擊 下擊！好像鐘擺上上下下
Downtown, uptown, as the clock winds down!
- 手舉起來 下巴壓低 - 蹲低一點 蹲低一點
- Hands up, chin down. - Stay low, stay low!
只剩5秒鐘 拳王使出了活塞式的組合拳
Only five seconds left, as here comes that piston-packed right of the champ!
鈴聲響起了 不敢相信 Atom竟然撐過了第一回合
There's the bell! I don't believe it. Somehow Atom has survived.
竟然進到了第二回合 觀眾都起雞皮疙瘩了
We will have a second round. And the crowd here is thrilled!
他辦到了！ 耶！ 回來角落！
He made it! Yeah! Corner!
我們要趕快離開這里 馬上！
We got to get out of here. We got to get out of here now!
走另外一邊 快點！
We got to go this way. Come on!
好吧 你坐下吧！
OK, you sit down.
- 走吧 宅男 - 好啦
- Let's go, homey. - All right.
我一會就回來 寶貝
I'll be back for you, baby.
把你的手拿開 我自己走
Get your hands off me!
二個角落都在忙的檢查他們的機器人
Both corners furiously working on their bots.
觀眾們本來都預期今晚是個大屠殺
This crowd came here tonight expecting a massacre,
但是迎來的是一場勢均力敵的戰斗
but instead they're getting a war!
- 你弄好了嗎？- 耶
- You got it? - Yeah.
好樣的 來吧！繼續！
All right. Here we go.
怎么搞的？
What is happening?
他已經完全準備好應付任何突發狀況 沒有事的
He is fully prepared for all possible contingencies. He will be fine.
然后呢？
What next?
第二回合
Round two.
Atom 第二回合 Atom 不可思議的挑戰者
Round two kicks off, and incredibly the challenger, Atom,
勇敢的挑戰拳王
is giving the champ a run for his money.
宙斯揣著小巨人 把它像個罐子丟到繩邊
Zeus tosses the smaller bot across the ring like a tin can!
肯頓讓他的機器人打出一個三連擊 打在拳王的臉上！
Kenton working his bot with a trifecta of straight rights to the champ's dome!
他們并列在戰場 震耳欲聾的歡呼聲
Toe-to-toe they stand, trading deafening blows!
不管繩圈旁的教練想什么伎倆都沒有用了
Whatever strategy either corner had cooked up has been destroyed!
金屬對戰金屬 鋼鐵大戰鋼鐵
Metal bashing metal. Steel smashing steel.
這是一場大戰
This is a brawl!
觀眾已經都站起來了 拉長脖子看二個機器人殘殺對方
The crowd is on their feet, watching two machines driven to kill each other!
也即將要發生什么大事了
Something has to give, and it does!
Atom 又一次倒下了
Atom goes down again!
今晚再一次次的點亮惡斗的戰場
Lights out for the junkyard dog who put on a heck of a show here tonight!
又一次 Atom又站起來了
And yet again, Atom rises up.
肯頓逼不得已要跳線接上 才可以使機器人回到比賽
Kenton must have hardwired this bot with the will to go on!
第四回合中段 拳王想馬上擊倒對手 結束比賽
Midway through round four, and Zeus is looking to end this thing right now.
拳王已經豁出一切 好像不打算回到更衣室了
The champ is holding nothing back as he cracks open the hurt locker!
Atom在繩索邊搖搖晃晃 他已經昏了！
Atom is stumbling around the ring, apparently disoriented and dazed!
- 手舉起來！ - 出了什么事？
- Hands up! - What's going on?
我猜語音控制已經壞掉了 沒有反應！
I think the voice recog is shot! He's not responding!
宙斯就像完美的暴力武器 鉆進Atom的腹部
Zeus has found yet another gear of violence, drilling Atom's midsection.
不！住手！幫一下手啊！
No! Stop! Do something!
他已經聽不到了！
He can't hear me!
但是鈴聲又響起了 小機器人的表現已經震驚了整個世界
But the bell sounds, and once again this little robot has stunned the world!
我們完蛋了 Max 他聽不到我的語音指揮了 這是謀殺 我們認輸吧！
We're done, Max! He can't hear me. This is murder. We've had enough.
- 我把語音辨識關掉了 - 又怎樣？他聽不到我的聲音了
- I'm disabling the voice recognition. - He can't hear me!
- 是的 但是他看得到你！ - 你說什么？
- Yes, but he can see you! - What?
我切換到映射模式 你要教他怎么做
I'm putting him in shadow mode. Show him what to do.
不用語音辨識模式 它可以移動的更快
Without the voice recognition, he'll move even faster!
不行 不行！
No way. No way!
看看他們 他們已經被打暈了！
Look at them. They are freaking out!
那個有錢女孩已經抓著他指指點點了！
Rich girl is ripping him a new one over there!
你知道為什么嗎？因為他們已經害怕了
Do you know why? Because they're scared.
因為Atom可以做到其他機器人做不到的
Because Atom can do things no other bot has ever done.
- 但是我做不到 - 行的 你可以的
- But I can't do it! - Yes, you can.
- 我不行啦 - 不 你行的
- I can't. - Yes, you can.
讓他知道怎么做 你必須自己戰斗最后一個回合
Show him what to do. You have to fight the last round.
不要拜托我 不要
Don't ask me. Don't.
Charlie... 拜托 我求你
Charlie... please. I beg you.
你要用那個小狗眼神“殺”死我？
Are you kidding me with those eyes?
該死的！
Damn it!
耶！
Yes!
真不敢相信我會這么做
I can't believe I'm doing this.
我知道你能了解 不管你是不是聽得到
I know you're in there! I'm not sure if you're getting this or what,
但是我確定你了解
but I know you're in there!
- 肯頓 打還是不打？- 打 給我一分鐘
- Kenton. In or out? - In. Give me a minute.
我知道你聽不見我說的 但是你可以看得到我 所以看著我
I know you can't hear me, but you can see me, so watch me!
仔細看著...我
Watch... me.
- 你知道你是對一個機器人講話 - 我知道 閉嘴！
- You know you're talking to a robot. - I know. Shut up.
注意看著我
Watch me.
這場如史詩般的大戰已經
An epic battle being waged here tonight,
馬上要進入第五回合 最后的一個回合
as the fifth and final round gets underway.
來吧 Atom！
Come on, Atom!
等一下 你有沒有看到？
Wait a second. Are you seeing this?
Charlie肯頓正在場外映射指導回擊
Charlie Kenton is shadowboxing just outside the ring!
看來Atom有動作映射功能
It looks like Atom has a shadow function.
所以基本上 Charlie肯頓就像是
So, basically, that means Charlie Kenton
在最后一個回合自己上場對抗宙斯
is fighting the last round of this fight against Zeus.
但是看起來一點幫助都沒有 Atom又被逼到了角落
It doesn't seem to help, because Atom is backed up against the ropes again.
幫幫他！ 還擊！
Help him! Fight back!
還不到時候
Not yet.
松本親自監督宙斯的操作人員
Tak Mashido supervising personally as Zeus hammers down,
憤怒的想馬上擊倒Atom 結束比賽
furiously trying to end this thing once and for all.
告訴各位大家 拳王看起來累了
I got to tell you, folks, the champ looks tired.
拳王看起來已經沒力了
This robot seems to be running on empty.
不敢相信！Atom在挑釁宙斯
I don't believe it. Atom is taunting Zeus.
- 切換到渦輪加速！ - 他認為還不夠！
- Switch to turbo! - He's actually asking for more.
拜托救救他！
Please do something!
- 還不到時候 - 對了 Charlie 還沒到時候
- Not yet. - That's right, Charlie. Not yet.
現在使出活塞拳！
Nitrous pistons, now!
他已經沒有辦法再支持住了
He's not going to last much longer!
- 回擊！ - 還不到時候
- Fight back! - Not yet.
堅持住！
Hang in there!
Atom對宙斯的機關槍拳一點都沒有辦法招架
Atom is riddled with the nitrous-fueled Gatling guns of Zeus's blows!
Atom！ Atom！ Atom！ Atom！
Atom! Atom! Atom! Atom!
等他沒力 等他力竭！ 還沒！
Wait him out, wait him out! Not yet!
宙斯慢下來了！
Zeus is slowing down!
拳王的動力已經接近報廢了
The champ's power core is clearly depleted.
Charlie 拜托！
Charlie, please!
嗨 小鬼！
Hey, kid.
- 時候到了 - 現在！
- Now. - Now!
靠近他！
Get in there!
揍扁這個婊子 打的他開花！
Knock that little bitch! Bust him open!
耶！ 這就對了！
Yeah! That's right!
想想辦法！！
Do something!
走開！
Move!
最高級別 切換到手動控制！
Override. Switching to manual.
松本吃驚的舉動 他竟然親手手動操作他的機器人
In a shocking move, Tak Mashido is manually operating his robot personally!
- 攻擊身體！ 靠近他！ - 打倒他 Atom！
- Work the body! Get inside him! - Get him, Atom!
大家看啊！拳王現在只能拼命的想辦法站著
Look at this! The champ is trying desperately to stay on his feet,
但是肯頓一點都不留情 一拳一拳的轟炸宙斯的身體！
but Kenton is relentless, landing blow after blow after blow to the body!
左！右！左！右！
Left! Right! Left! Right!
Atom打出一記重要的上勾拳！ 宙斯倒下了！
A huge uppercut by Atom! Zeus is down!
這個小機器人今天晚上的頑強表現
This little bot has dug deep here tonight
深深的觸動每一個人的心
and shown something damn near heart!
1 2 3......
One, two, three,
4 5 6 7......
four, five, six, seven...
宙斯站起來了！
He's good!
宙斯已經快站不住了 但是肯頓及...
Zeus gets to his feet, but Kenton has Atom on him again,
...Atom沒有放過他 拳如雨下！
landing punch after punch!
松本跟他的超級機器人一點都沒有辦法回應
Tak Mashido and his super bot have no answer.
宙斯夾住了Atom的左臂 但是肯頓一點都不懼怕
Zeus pins Atom's left arm, but Kenton is undaunted!
局面竟然到了這個地步 各位！
It all comes down to this, folks!
甩開他 Charlie！ 就是現在！
Drop him, Charlie! Now!
- 肯頓已經快把冠軍... - 不 鈴聲響起來了
- Kenton is about to drop the champ... - No! There's the bell!
鈴聲救了宙斯！！
Zeus is saved by the bell!
不可思議 比賽進入到裁判判決
Amazingly, we will go to the judges' cards!
去吧！
各位先生女士們 經過了五個艱苦的回合以后
Ladies and gentlemen, after five rounds,
裁判的判決已經出來了
we go to the judges' scorecards.
第一位裁判的判決 47-48
Judge Number One scores the fight 47-48.
第二位裁判的判決 48-46
Judge Number Two scores the fight 48-46.
第三為裁判的判決 47-46
And Judge Number Three scores the fight 47-46,
世界冠軍成功的保住了他的冠軍頭銜
for the winner and still World Robot Boxing champion,
宙斯！
Zeus!
法拉 蘭蔻娃
Farra Lemkova,
妳的機器人今天晚上的表現比你們說的差多了
you got way more than you bargained for tonight.
有人說你的機器人贏了判決 但是輸了比賽
Some would say that your bot won the decision but lost the fight.
她看起來很不爽
She looks pissed.
比賽過程比我們想象的還要久一點
It took a little longer than we thought,
但是結果還是如預期的一樣
but the result is as expected.
我們贏了 宙斯還是永遠不敗的
We won. Zeus is still undefeated.
松本先生 我想問的是...
對于你們今晚這場那么羞辱的比賽 被慘痛的修理...
Any comment on the absolutely humiliating near loss
...還差點輸了 你有沒有話要說？
your bot suffered tonight?
- 沒說 - 不予置評
- Nothing. - No comment.
Max Max在哪里？
Max. Where's Max?
他在那里...Max！
There he is. Max.
大家都稱你的機器人是“平民冠軍"
They're already calling your bot "the people's champion."
你怎么說呢？
What do you say to that?
平民冠軍？
People's champion?
對我來說 很好！
Sounds pretty good to me.
爹？爹！
Dad? Dad!
爹！
Dad!
我真的想讓你知道
I really want you to know...
不 你需要知道...
No, I need you to know.
不用擔心
Don't worry.
我會保密的
Your secret's safe with me.
等一下！
Wait here. Wait here.
耶！
Yes!
翻譯：閑閑的猛男 校對：目前沒有